(The last round of Fact Land Grab)
(Only two questions are left.)
O.
Correct.
- Yes!
- It's Busan.
- Skip the turn now.
She can just skip the turn.
- It's a tie.
- Do we win if she answers it?
- Yes.
(Only one question remains.)
I choose C3.
(According to
UN's Food and Agriculture Organization,)
(coffee is the second most consumed
beverage in the world after water.)
I don't think that's true.
- I think it'd be tea.
- Coke.
It might be coffee.
You never know.
- I have no idea.
- I think it's Coke.
- It could be coffee.
- It's not Coke.
- No?
- It's either tea or coffee,
and I think it's coffee.
(According to
UN's Food and Agriculture Organization,)
(coffee is the second most consumed
beverage in the world after water.)
O.
- Let's go, the heart of a beast.
- Let's go!
- The heart of a beast!
I think it's tea.
My heart hurts.
Incorrect.
- Yes!
- We won!
- What?
- Who won?
Did he win?
- This is unreal.
- A one-point difference.
For real?
(Groaning)
That was tough.
Round Three of Fact Land Grab is over.
Here are the results.
Team Gold, 24 points.
Team White, 25 points.
Team White won.
Seriously.
It was a real bummer.
To lose by just one question.
I had caught up so much.
Had the alliance team not had the items,
we would've definitely won.
"Please get it wrong."
"Please believe that it's coffee."
I was shaking all over.
I kept silently hoping
she'd get it wrong...
and counting only the numbers
she got right.
Solving the question was
the least of my concerns.
"Win with your skills."
"Just win,"
was what we talked about a lot.
Skills weren't what helped me win today.
I used two pricey weapons.
I barely won by doing so.
I couldn't be over the moon about it.
Of course, winning the war was...
great news for the team.
But I'm still ashamed.
(Episode 10: The Perfect Victory)
The final result of Fact Land Grab.
Having won 2 rounds out of the 3,
- Team White has won the war.
- Thank you.
- Well done.
It would've been sadder
had it been 2 to 0.
The winning team...
claims half
of the losing team's total assets...
as spoils of war.
The total spoils that
Team Gold must give to...
Team White are as follows.
Ninety-nine diamonds, eight lives,
five credits, and seventy-five gold.
They really didn't do anything.
Teams White and Red,
please discuss
how you would like to divide the spoils.
The transfer of the spoils
will take place...
at the Community Center shortly.
Team Gold wasn't bluffing about
how many resources they had at all.
From what I saw, Team Gold had
enough lives to survive until the end.
That was what could've put them at ease.
I felt a sense of disconnect there.
After checking the amount of spoils,
it became much clearer.
The transfer of the spoils will now begin.
(Transfer of the Spoils)
The losing team is to check
the amount of spoils...
and submit them in the central box.
The winning team is
to collect the spoils...
from the slot.
(Team Red collects
all the credits and lives.)
(Team White collects
all the diamonds and gold.)
The spoils transfer has been completed.
As of this moment,
the state of war has been lifted.
The leader negotiation will now begin.
First off,
here's the pollution index for...
the entire Community Town.
The total pollution index
accumulated over the past seven days...
is 70.
Please note that
once the pollution index reaches 100,
the town will be considered saturated.
Personally, I did want to experience...
the pollution event.
It's said to be deadly, so I wonder
how much danger it could cause.
But I can't put the community at risk
just because of my curiosity.
Even if we use up all the credits
currently available in the market,
we won't exceed the pollution limit.
Here is the agenda for
the leader negotiation.
The first agenda item is...
the no-war treaty.
(First agenda item: No-war treaty)
As of today, Day Seven,
two wars have broken out
within the Community Town,
causing damage to several town members.
If 3 of the 5 leaders agree,
no further wars may be declared for
the remainder of the period.
It'd be too selfish of me,
so I'm staying still.
If there were no wars,
I'd be at a loss as the weapon dealer.
This isn't something I could say
as someone who started a war.
It will sound very hypocritical.
The first war broke out...
due to survival.
The second war was also...
(Team White declares war on...)
(Team Gold.)
Part of the reason was for survival.
Our safety...
wasn't guaranteed until the end.
Who knows what kind of variables...
there may be until the final goal,
but I no longer want a war to survive.
In Team Gold's shoes,
you may think,
"Didn't you declare war against us?"
"Taking away the chance
to take your spoils is absurd."
This is simply my opinion.
I can't tell what's right at the moment.
I simply stated my opinion
after reading that agenda item.
(Leia agrees with the no-war treaty.)
What do you think, Reboot?
I do see the need...
for the no-war treaty,
but is there really a need to...
forcibly ban it by making it a treaty?
(Reboot disagrees with the no-war treaty.)
I understand the purpose of it.
From where we stand, the other teams
can declare war and are justified.
But since we joined later,
we can't declare war even if we want to.
In a way, it's like...
the environmental regulations
by the big powers.
But...
you don't have enough for tomorrow.
And I mean lives.
We're not short of it.
- What?
- You're not short of it?
Don't you have 3 left
after submitting 5 today?
Yes.
(3 lives remain after submitting 5)
Feel free to tell us your thoughts.
Is Team Gold's opinion that
concluding the treaty isn't necessary?
I see it as unnecessary.
I'm...
against it.
What?
I don't think there's a need
for the no-war treaty.
It's totally fine
even if war breaks out tomorrow.
As this is a survival show,
our team will win
with an absolute winning method.
I don't want to create any variables.
I'm even thinking of
starting a war tomorrow.
Hence, I'm against the no-war treaty.
Those who are against the no-war treaty,
please raise your hand.
(3 teams are against the no-war treaty.)
- We're done here.
- Okay, got it.
Speaking on behalf of my team,
although we haven't been here
for very long,
before we can even think about
whether we can do well,
we're faced with
a more fundamental question.
Can we actually play the game?
There was no Gold Rush
when we had just joined.
You all even voted that gold
wasn't acceptable at the supermarket.
What's more, you decided
not to sell any food to us.
With that, the rest were reluctant
to trade with us.
Distribution was almost nonexistent,
which made the game impossible to play.
We joined...
within relationships shaped by...
vested interests among the others.
The basic conditions for competition
should have been in place.
Honestly, it was hard to see
how we could play the game...
in a situation
where competition wasn't taking place.
There obviously needs to be
a more forward-looking attitude.
I dearly hoped you would eat today.
It was a choice we made,
so you're not entirely to blame.
I've rarely gone without food
for this long.
Honestly speaking, it is tough.
But that's not what got me enraged.
The part that made me think
things weren't right was...
him telling the other teammates,
"Buy gold, and I'm cutting off food."
I feel that was very unjust.
I didn't eat as a way of protesting.
Are you planning to starve
tomorrow as well?
That's something my team...
- will decide.
- Of course.
The supermarket is open,
and the food is free.
Feel free to come and eat.
Why the sudden change of heart?
Since we brought it up yesterday,
you could've come
with a light heart today.
Here's what frustrated me the most.
Team Gold begs the question...
and isn't willing to communicate.
That boosted the distrust I had.
We concluded that
you weren't willing to talk to us.
But asking us to make it
so that you can take part in the game?
Personally, it's hard to understand.
There was plenty of
space and time for us to talk,
but the one who refused to communicate...
wasn't us. It was Team Gold.
Honestly, I wanted to agree to
the no-war treaty.
That would help us feel at ease
for tomorrow...
and secure our victory more.
But Team Gold said they didn't feel...
they had a fair chance to play,
that none of the teams
were being cooperative,
and that the game had been structured
to prevent them...
from participating
from the moment they joined.
Team Gold had plenty of opportunities.
It's a real shame
they couldn't seize them.
The moment I heard that,
I wanted another war.
There is definitely a difference in
perspective there as well.
I believe we didn't give it our all
and didn't have the capability to do so.
If we had circulated gold
and traded with each other,
then asking,
"Why are you being so passive?"
"Why are you so isolated?"
would have been a fair
and understandable criticism.
But they blocked that circulation
for two days.
You can still find...
plenty of examples today of people
using arguments...
to defend their own interests
and preserve the vested interests...
of the old system.
Either way,
can we move on from this treaty?
- No no-war treaty.
- Sure.
We have disagreed on...
the no-war treaty.
Negotiation failed.
War is not prohibited.
(No-war treaty negotiation failed)
Next is whether to provide aid
or impose sanctions.
I have a question.
Is food trading included in the sanctions?
Food trading is not included in
the sanctions.
Team Red wants to...
sanction Team Gold
for resource trading tomorrow.
Team Gold wanted to maintain war,
meaning they wanted to keep
playing the game.
Fine then. I'll do my best.
To make Team Diamond win,
I will use every means possible.
As wars are allowed,
I want to impose a sanction.
There was no reason to hold back
on the other things either.
They could think,
"Aren't you making us play with..."
"both hands and feet tied?"
But we have two more days left.
Nobody can imagine
what kind of variables could pop up.
We should widen the gap
at this very moment.
- I agree.
I disagree.
Shut everything down completely,
and they might just be going through
a few days of trial and error...
before they're actually ready
to make a move.
"Don't close the final door."
"Let's give them a chance."
"We shouldn't ban them outright."
I opposed it on those grounds.
Just as court rulings include
a minority opinion,
I wanted to make sure my position was
also on the record.
The sanction has been imposed.
Team Gold can't trade for a day tomorrow.
It's true that I was taken aback.
What I can't grasp even now is that...
sanctions are imposed...
when someone does something wrong
and a reason is given.
But I did not hear any reasons.
The vote still passed.
Even with the way...
this community's voting system
is structured,
it still reveals how much power...
the stronger players have
to push down those...
who are newer or in a weaker position.
I couldn't help but have
that somewhat bitter thought.
All discussions have ended.
We'll move on to today's life submission.
(The one-person groups,
Blue and White, are eliminated.)
(Day 7 Life Submission)
(Everyone in Team Red survives Day 7.)
Let's toughen up.
Please check the contents
of the central box...
and allocate the lives.
(Day 7 Life Submission)
(Reboot's life hasn't been submitted.)
(Day 7 Life Submission:
Mokgye, Luna, Maetel, Ugong)
The life was not submitted for
Reboot today.
What?
The resident whose life
was not submitted...
must leave now.
Why is he leaving?
Why did he do that?
Why is he making it hard for us?
- Did you hear that?
- Did you just hear that?
Why would he make a move like this?
Does he want the four of us to survive
until tomorrow?
Is there any meaning behind it?
He should've fought until the last moment.
Of course, it's for each of us to decide.
No wonder he asked me
whether the leader would leave...
if he didn't allocate one to the leader.
(Reboot returns to the dormitory
after submitting the lives for Day 7.)
I should still pass on the information.
Honestly, I don't understand why...
you made such a decision.
I should pass on the information.
I'll share the information and my opinion.
I'll go call Ugong.
I disagreed with the agenda item
to conclude a no-war treaty.
Team Red disagreed.
The leader disagreed with
the no-war treaty.
So did Team Blue.
In the end,
there will be no no-war treaty.
In short, it was voted down.
Did Team White agree to it?
Team White did say that
it was necessary in a way.
Of course, she felt bad about it.
- Ultimately,
- Ultimately...
let's not make a treaty banning it.
It was voted down 2 to 3.
After that,
Team Red wanted to impose a sanction...
when it came to providing aid
or imposing sanctions.
He suggested imposing...
a sanction
on Team Gold's trading tomorrow.
That was agreed upon.
But that's not just limited to
the supermarket.
It includes everything tomorrow,
including the Platform trading.
In short, the number of resources
won't change.
From what I see, I think Team Red
did that to get back at me...
out of some...
- ill feelings.
- That's why he imposed a sanction?
And so it was approved.
By approved, you mean...
- it passed, right?
- Yes, it passed.
- Now...
- Can we not use our gold?
We can't make any trades all day tomorrow.
It's a sanction.
- Tomorrow's the last day.
- Yes, a sanction for tomorrow.
It could be that Team Red...
already had that in mind
and imposed it at a bad time.
- It's just my opinion.
- Whatever the trigger was,
- it doesn't matter.
- What matters is that it was approved.
Yes, that's what matters.
But the fact that it was brought about
right now is...
- It's absurd.
- Yes, it's absurd.
Tomorrow's game will be meaningless.
If Team Red did it spontaneously,
why did Teams Black and Blue agree
to impose a sanction on us?
It leaves me with that question.
They knew they'd win
and wanted to secure it.
I'm not sure about that.
I don't think this is right.
What now?
This is so wrong.
This is so unfair
that I'm actually in tears.
The way I see it,
there's a possibility that
Team Red brought it up spontaneously.
But I'm not too sure.
I'm not sure what intentions he had
in bringing it up.
I was quite shocked myself...
after hearing the result.
I couldn't stop it.
The decision was made by voting.
I'm going to go cheer her up.
Luna.
It's okay. It's just a game.
They're making the game so dirty.
- Doing so...
- It's okay. It's just a game.
A game should be played like one.
What is this
if we're going to do things like this?
Maybe we have to see this through
for something to come of it.
- We have to hit rock bottom...
- They're nasty.
I'm so angry that I'm in tears.
It's okay.
I'm so frustrated I'm in tears.
More things in life will make you angry.
This is nothing.
Cry if you want to.
Crying might make you feel better.
Our team couldn't even trade,
to begin with.
The other teams weren't trading with us
on purpose.
But was it necessary
to impose this sanction on us?
I don't know what they were trying to do.
Do they just want to fight?
At this point, they just hate us.
It's personal.
I'd like to say two things here.
First,
my actions here led
to certain situations unfolding.
And you must have been hurt by them.
I failed to see the consequences...
of my actions,
and I didn't do enough
to apologize for my actions.
For that, I'm deeply sorry.
I'm very sad to hear that you're leaving.
A big part of me feels guilty too.
First of all,
I'm telling you this person-to-person.
As for the second thing I want to say,
if I'm being honest,
your decision makes me think...
that you're being irresponsible.
We're a team.
We were all trying our best
to survive here.
But your departure only crushed our hopes.
With your decision,
you're robbing us even of our hopes now.
On top of that, you're the leader.
You're passing the buck,
which is an irresponsible act.
There are winners and losers in games.
That's the nature.
We might still end up as losers,
but we'd be losers who did their best.
Of course, things look hopeless now.
But we could have kept trying to the end.
And some of us hadn't given up.
Why are you making
the rest of us give up too?
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I'll give what you said
some serious thought.
Before making this decision,
I thought long and hard about it.
But from my point of view,
there are basic principles
people should stick to.
Anyway, there were some things...
I wanted to address.
And my sole focus was to bring them up,
to be honest.
At the Leader Negotiation,
I felt like I hit a massive wall.
According to the basic standards I have,
it was irrational.
He was using food, which was
a basic necessity, for his own gain.
Involving the basic element
of human survival...
was something I personally
couldn't tolerate.
I couldn't accept myself staying here...
and playing the game.
I want to apologize to you the most...
for not staying here with you...
and not giving you a heads-up.
For that, I'm truly sorry.
I'd like to ask you once again
to try to understand my decision.
We lost, and we were running low on lives.
If I had stayed, we would've had
only three left by tomorrow.
We would've been okay
if we got more lives.
But without new lives,
two of us would have to leave.
So I decided to leave the game today.
That way, the four of them...
could survive to the end.
That was my wish.
If someone had to leave,
it made more sense for me
to take responsibility and leave the game.
Reboot kept mentioning
problems with the system...
and pointed out the flawed attitudes
of the other teams.
As an act of protest,
he decided to leave.
I still wonder if that was
the only decision he could have made.
I understand his decision.
When it comes to this game,
if it starts to diverge
from your core beliefs and principles...
or crosses the line you can tolerate,
although everyone might have
a different threshold...
for where the line is,
as long as
you no longer see this as right,
it becomes a matter of freedom.
When I heard what happened
during the Leader Negotiation...
and what he tried to get across
to the other leaders,
I could understand his decision even more.
He didn't have to apologize to us.
It looked like
he was trying to convey the message...
that something was terribly wrong
about the system...
by voluntarily dropping out of the game.
I just wanted to respect his decision.
I should get going now.
The announcement was made.
The principles of market economy...
are interlinked with the principles
of capitalism from our Constitution.
It gives us freedom
and a system to thrive in.
Our profits are maximized through trade.
In the utilitarian sense,
everyone in the community can be happy.
With that purpose,
this system was implemented in society.
Over the years,
it's been modified and improved.
Just as expected,
when information isn't transparent...
and when people aren't
on an equal footing to compete,
while allowing people's greed
to take over,
our society would turn into chaos,
resembling the concept,
"The war of all against all."
We'd end up in a chaotic situation,
reverting back to a primitive society.
In the end, power is the law...
where brute force becomes justice
in this world.
So I spent a lot of time
thinking about my decision.
(Reboot)
(Morning of Day 8)
(Dormitory for Gold)
(Dormitory for White)
As soon as I woke up,
I could only think of one solution.
I wanted to talk to Team White...
and risk my place in the game.
I wanted to try to come up with a way
by giving more gold to Team White.
They're not here.
(Dormitory for Red)
- Yes?
- Hello. I see.
- Hello.
- Is Leia here?
- Yes?
Leia isn't here.
- Really?
- Yes.
Okay.
(Leia is getting ready in the dorm.)
I couldn't find her.
- You couldn't find her?
- No.
She wasn't in the center?
- No. No one was in there.
- Okay.
- Maybe she's just getting ready...
- Just during that time?
- in the dorm?
- What?
Anyway, Reboot...
- was our leader up until yesterday.
- Okay.
Now that our leader is gone,
we have to pick another leader.
Halfway through yesterday,
the player who led the most...
It was like a coup.
Mokgye was leading our team.
If you agree to appoint her as the leader,
raise your hands.
I agree.
Thank you. I'll do my best.
(Mokgye becomes the leader on Day 8.)
I tried to find Leia this morning.
Leia didn't seem happy yesterday.
Of course, we're competing here
for our personal gain.
But we also need to consider
what's right for this community.
That should be another agenda.
And I'm sure this matter is
on Leia's mind.
"Is this the right direction
of our community?"
That's what I'm going to ask her first.
Donkey will have to share his prize
with Vector.
That way, Donkey can be...
the last surviving member of White.
We can accept Leia, Paul, and Siseon.
This is the best we can do.
We can form a new team with them
and share the gains.
Then just like yesterday,
they'll say that...
we're not making any sacrifices
while they are.
They'll say something like that.
Then I'll say...
I'm going to take responsibility.
I'm going to tell her
that I won't submit a life for myself.
My plan was...
to have gold as the final resource
by ensuring...
the alliance between White and Gold...
through relocation.
I thought we'd be able to...
come to an agreement
by sacrificing my gains.
- That's the only solution I have for now.
- That's...
(They haven't returned to their team
after yesterday's war.)
There's not an easy day here.
They should've imposed a sanction
to prevent wars.
But the players of Team Gold said...
it wasn't fair to prevent any future wars.
So the sanction to prevent wars...
I really don't understand them.
They should've imposed the sanction
to prevent any future wars.
They should try to trade
through the Platform...
No. Their leader told me
he wanted the option to start a war.
That's why I stopped them
from doing any trades today.
Then I really don't understand
their decision.
- As long as war is still on the table,
- Okay.
the risk can't be contained.
Well, they'll probably want to start a war
after running the scenarios in their head.
Shockingly enough,
there will be another war today.
Yesterday's war was about...
checking their resources
and acquiring their lives.
That's why we started the war.
As for today,
we already divided up the diamonds.
But if they start the war,
we'll end up losing a lot of the diamonds.
They might not start it.
But if we rely on that possibility,
there's a risk of an uneven distribution.
The only reason behind our alliance is...
that the eight of us will end up...
with the same amount of money
as our prize.
If Team Gold...
were to come after one of our teams,
one of us would end up with less money.
To prevent that,
we have to start the war first.
By now, they know that
they don't stand a chance. Right?
- That's why they brought up...
- It's really over now.
- Right. I...
- It's really over.
I'll be honest.
Starting another war with them...
would be crossing the line.
After listening to
the leader of Team Gold earlier,
I've changed my mind.
I do see the need for the no-war treaty,
but is there really a need to...
forcibly ban it by making it a treaty?
Just like we did today, we'll hit them
first by starting another war.
We'll kill them all,
so Team Gold has zero chance of winning.
I'll go with the plan
that will guarantee our team's victory.
I'll hit them with the bomb...
before the war.
I won't leave anything to chance.
It will be a total victory.
To make sure
we don't lose anything from the war,
we have to move all the diamonds
from Blue to Red.
Then Blue has to start the war.
As for the share of the diamonds,
we can return them to her through aid
after the war.
Everyone will end up
with the same number of diamonds.
Starting this war is
absolutely necessary to us.
They said
they wanted the option to start wars.
Yes.
I thought, "Really? They want to have
another war on the last day too?"
"All right.
I'll cripple one of your hands."
That's why I imposed the sanction on them.
Okay.
Why is Luna with Team White?
- That's what we need to talk about.
- Really?
- Leia...
- Yes.
and I...
That's what you guys want?
I think she's really sorry
about how things panned out.
Considering everything,
we want to persuade Luna to join us.
We want to end on a good note together
as players of Team White.
Actually, the game is over.
There's nothing Team Gold can do now.
A lot of things already happened...
at yesterday's Leader Negotiation.
We practically cut off their limbs.
We thought if that was the case,
we should bring back Luna.
Team Gold won't have any lives left
after tonight.
So I spent a lot of time...
trying to convince Red
so they'd agree to our plan to bring Luna.
If everything goes well...
and she were to split the gains with us,
we wouldn't have to change
the number of diamonds you guys take.
- You guys would split your gains?
- We're going to split...
- our gains with her.
- You'll do that?
That's how deeply you care about Luna.
- Right.
- That's how we felt.
Then, regarding this matter,
let me talk to her first...
- before today's productive activities.
- Okay.
- And we'll update you right away.
- Her opinion is also important.
- Yes.
- You won't do the quizzes today?
- No.
- Okay.
- All right.
I'll request for relocation now.
- We have to relocate to Blue.
- To Blue.
- Blue.
- For that.
- Just for that.
- Let's do our best.
You guys have to follow the plan, though.
Use six credits for the bidding.
- Pitou has to do it, right?
- Yes.
Use one to start the quizzes.
- Two hints. Okay.
- Two credits for the hints.
- We must have 11 credits at the end.
- Okay.
- We just need to use two.
- Without them,
we can't hit them with the bomb.
(Hints: 2, Bidding: 6,
Ticket: 1, Bomb: 10)
Today's production activity
will begin shortly.
There's ongoing resource depletion
within the Community Town.
Only one production site is open
for production.
The bidding for this one production site
will begin now.
- We'll bid six.
- Okay.
Relocate quickly.
- Let's relocate quickly.
- Okay.
Blue has to go down to make a bid.
I'd like to relocate to Team White.
Okay. I'll accept the request.
I'd like to relocate to Team Blue.
I'd like to relocate to Team Blue
and produce a lot of lives.
Okay.
(Donkey, Izaha, and Siseon
relocate to Team Blue.)
I need to bring some credits with me.
What about us?
Should we bid for the production site?
- Let's talk to them about that.
- Okay.
- Let's ask them why they need more lives.
- Let's ask them.
We can only decide
if we should participate in...
the production activity today or not...
- after talking to them first.
- But...
so many people have already relocated
to Blue for the production activity.
- It means they're highly motivated.
- It means they will do it.
Anyway, we should let them know
that we need lives too.
No, they think that we don't need lives
when it's just us.
We have four lives.
- Right. We don't need any lives.
- Right.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
"Why do you want to get more lives?"
- They might feel that way.
- That's possible.
"We'll go in, so you shouldn't."
If we say that,
- they might not understand us.
- We don't need to get more lives.
We don't have any leverage to use
when it comes to bidding.
Should I relocate to Blue
and solve the quizzes with them?
- Why?
- To get more lives.
What if it becomes
an integrated community?
- Is that pointless?
- No.
Their alliance hasn't changed yet.
- But...
- It's an interesting offer.
- Should we try that?
- There's a possibility...
that she might not come back
after relocating.
- So...
- Why wouldn't I come back?
- I see.
- To get the prize?
But that's...
Here's the thing. It's over for us.
There's no way of staying here.
- So...
- They won't let us in...
- They won't.
- given the current situation.
That's the point.
We already lost,
- and asking them to take us now...
- Exactly.
- That's why we don't need to do that.
- Yes.
- We don't need to get more lives.
- But...
When she said it,
she wasn't trying to make a point.
She just meant to say
she wanted to play games before leaving.
- That was her point.
- I have no airtime now.
Why don't you go and ask them?
- We need to show them we changed too.
- But...
we're too late to change.
- That's what they're saying.
- But...
- You know what?
- Yes.
Let's not just stay here like before.
- Let's go out.
- Let's please go out.
- Let's go and face them.
- But...
(Away)
- Good morning.
- Hello.
Are you going to use this?
Today.
- I'll give it to you as soon as I open.
- Okay.
No? Right.
- Hello.
- There's no mercy.
- Good morning.
Are you here to make a bid?
Well, there's only one production site.
You're going there. So there's no point.
- We came down to talk.
- That's great.
- Just to talk.
- The weather is great today.
- A clear day after a rainy day.
- Right.
How many of you are going? Four?
- Is it just you guys?
- Yes, the four of us are going.
- Should we get going?
- We...
Right. We need to get going.
We have about five minutes left.
How many...
- I think we can just bid one.
- Let's play it safe.
If they're not going to bid,
I think we can just bid one.
But let's play it safe.
We can't risk any damage
in case they bid at the last minute.
Then let's wait in front of the door.
- Should we?
- Yes.
- I don't want to waste the credits.
- Sure.
Can we join you
just to participate in the quizzes?
You should've relocated.
Is it not allowed now?
- I thought we could do it anytime.
- We can do that now, can't we?
- We don't have much time left.
- Right.
- We're running out of time.
- That's...
Well, I just want to join you...
- and solve the quizzes with you.
- Right.
- I won't even pack.
- I see.
- How many minutes do we have left?
- I guess time's up.
I guess it's about to end now.
There are three minutes left
to bid on the production site.
- She needs to bid first.
- Should I ask her?
- Blue.
- Yes?
Can I just join you for the quizzes
and leave right away?
I won't even pack.
I'm really going to leave...
- after that.
- She just wants to solve the quizzes.
I'm a bit worried, though.
By the way, that's my thing.
I'm a worrywart.
I'm worried that you might not leave.
- Let me make a bid.
- Let's do that first.
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
- I'll just bid one.
- Okay. I'll stay here.
If you want to bid on a production site,
tell me the color of your team...
and submit the credits in the central box.
Please wait a bit.
I haven't made up my mind yet...
on how many I should bid.
Blue.
(Team Blue submits 1 credit.)
(Blue didn't use 6 credits,
which was the plan.)
Bidding for the production site
has closed.
Team Blue has won the bidding
for the production site.
- It's done.
- Good.
- Time's up, right?
- Yes.
- Great.
- I was in there until time ran out.
- Right. I thought so.
- I stalled for 20 seconds.
- Great job.
The production activity for Day Eight
has begun.
- Blue is going?
- Yes.
How many did you bid?
- One.
- Get four hints.
- Okay.
- You did the right thing by saving them.
- Yes.
Whenever he tells us to do something,
- I just say, "Yes, sir."
- "Yes, sir."
- I just know he knows what he's doing.
- I'm sure he has a good reason for it.
- Right.
- We'll be back.
- Okay.
Hello.
- We'll be back.
- I...
- Make a lot of money.
- Okay.
Izaha!
- He needs a minute.
- Wait.
Yes?
Use up to four.
If you can solve it with one credit,
then use it.
If we're completely sure,
- we can use one more?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(Team Production is
strictly following Maillard's order.)
Good.
What should we do?
I wonder what Gold is doing.
Why did they not bid
on the production site?
- The bidding?
- It'd be their loss.
- Because they can't win the bidding?
- Right.
They might have thought that
holding onto the credits would be better.
My gosh.
There will be a war today. Right?
Starting a war today will guarantee
our win.
Hitting them with the bomb
might trigger them...
to start the war.
- So we're striking first.
- Right.
It's like a warning shot...
before the war.
We'll have to hit them with the bomb.
We have no choice.
It doesn't matter whether or not
Team Gold ends up with 1 or 0.
The rest of them will have to leave
except for one.
If they win the war,
they can take our lives.
What if Blue loses?
- If she were to start the war,
- Okay.
she needs to have four with her.
In case she loses, she needs to have two.
That way, she uses one tonight
and uses the other one...
during the vote tomorrow.
Without wasting...
(They can hear Team Production's cheering
from the hub.)
They're going wild.
I guess they got it right.
They're so noisy.
- They're clapping.
I guess they're doing well today.
They at least got two lives.
That is correct.
(Correct)
- Wait.
- That's amazing.
- Siseon, that's so sexy.
- I knew it, Siseon!
- That's really sexy.
- We...
could never have guessed that right.
- Right. Only he could've gotten it right.
- It's my first time hearing it.
- My field of study...
- finally came up.
- No one could've gotten it but him.
- Gosh, at last.
- This was...
tailored for Siseon.
I think having more resources...
will definitely be an advantage.
- Right.
- We fought over resources from the start.
Exactly.
What's Team Gold dong?
- We barely got to talk.
- Right.
- The game is nearing its end now.
There were some things
we wanted to tell you.
We were informed about the agenda
from yesterday's negotiation...
right before he left.
He told you about them, right?
He did tell us about the agenda
from yesterday...
- and how the votes went.
- Okay.
There was a bit of complacency.
- It sounded like...
- It's like...
wanting to go to war was our main opinion.
- As talks progressed like that,
- That was the misunderstanding.
that misunderstanding piled up...
- to end up like this.
- We've never had those talks,
but we ended up...
- putting up walls against each other.
- Right.
Was the reason for declaring war
a shortage of lives?
No. We needed to know
if you guys were bluffing.
Bluffing about what?
Lives.
We weren't able to talk it out.
What was the first plan of Team Gold?
As soon as you guys appeared,
you revealed Black's identity.
You also thought about
blowing everything up.
You considered making gold...
- the main currency.
- Right.
- Actually...
- To be honest,
it's true that we were selfish.
There was a reason why we missed out.
We were starting a revolution.
We were contributing to making
a better society.
We had an idea that we deserved more.
Was it simply just an issue of proportion?
Well, that could be part of it.
It was because of stability.
I think we were focused on our own profit.
We even thought about this method.
The first idea was to persuade everyone,
including Team Red.
As Team Red has gained a lot of power
as the casting voter,
considering that they have become
too greedy,
the second idea was to join forces
only with Team White.
- I see.
- Right.
Are you going to declare war today?
- No. There's no reason for that.
- No.
- This is our last offer.
- Right.
So let's make things clear.
Team Red, Team Blue, and Team Black
will be excluded?
- No.
- No. Red can be included.
- They already have gold.
- Right.
Based on the gold they have,
it will be distributed equally.
If you feel that our team
has too many members,
I am willing to move.
- So what I wish to do...
- Right.
is to find the right balance.
So...
why is it better for us to live
in a world of gold in this process?
The reason you're trying to persuade me...
is that you're suggesting a move...
- to a better and more developed world.
- Right.
The reason why I feel torn...
is that I don't know why
that is a better world.
It's a transparent currency.
- Right.
- If you consider this a real society...
Think of it in that direction.
I don't think it's an issue about it
being transparent or not.
We don't have to be transparent
with our currency,
but we're doing that on our own.
I think it will be neater to say
that you guys wish to win as well.
I couldn't understand them.
I made this offer 2 or 3 days ago.
They made another offer
with the project of choosing gold.
And now,
I believe it's their last resort...
to go in that direction again.
"We wish to live,"
"but there's no other way."
"If we do this,"
"Team White or Team Red
can earn a better profit."
Putting it like this
would've sounded much more honest...
at this point.
There's one last offer we wish to make.
This was the conclusion we reached
after talking it through.
She did her best
when she was in Team White.
She had no choice but to act this way
because of the role she was given.
As with Luna,
we wish that...
you guys would embrace her in the end.
Luna doesn't know about this.
- We didn't want to make her feel bad.
- Right.
This was purely out of...
- humanitarian consideration, right?
- Right.
- Yes.
Please put some thought into that.
- That would be great.
- Right.
- I'll be honest.
I'm willing to take you back.
You tried to get me back, right?
Yes. That's why I'm here.
The only thing Team Gold can do
is declare war.
Right.
This is from my pure heart.
I felt so bad seeing you wither away.
"I'm a spy from Team Gold."
"Is it right for me to speak
with Team White?"
I believe you would've gone through
many different thoughts,
but I wish to allow you
to end as a Team White member.
You won't accept another member
from Team Gold, right?
I won't.
The other members of Team Gold
were already enemies.
They were enemies,
and they offered to save only me.
They believed that I was suffering
in this whole situation.
It was true that I was struggling,
but it wasn't because I was in Team Gold.
But actually,
- I was always a Team Gold member.
- Right.
I wanted to do my best
as a Team Gold member.
Excluding Team Gold...
was never an option for me,
- to be honest.
- Right.
That was why I wanted to help Team Gold
and Team White...
earn the greatest profit.
The best scenario that I came up with
was the one I shared with Leia.
Through the self-destruct project,
we will move at least two
of our members...
and live off gold.
- That was my idea.
- I also thought that was the best method.
That day was the greatest opportunity
for Team Gold.
- Right. But...
- The day Black caused chaos.
there was no way
for me to make that happen.
- I didn't have the right reasoning.
- But...
- All that was wanted from me...
- was to save Team White.
- you shouldn't have talked to the team.
You should've shared that with me as well.
All of this happened
because of a block in communication.
After today's conversation,
I realized all of this happened
because of the refusal...
to move into our team.
Realizing that made everything make sense.
The winner and loser were already decided,
and it felt like I lost without even
being able to compete.
- I struggled because of that.
- Right.
- I now know why everything has happened.
It doesn't matter if it happened
because of a misunderstanding...
or bad decision-making.
I just need to understand
why things happened this way.
After realizing that it was because
of a lack of my abilities,
I want to go back in time
to recover from this disappointment.
I love seeing you smile like this.
We did a great job with our roles.
- I did things to get information.
- Right.
Since you were a spy,
be a spy until the end.
Be a double spy.
Won't that be better?
To be honest,
everything has been decided
in my situation.
Well,
I don't wish to win like that.
That isn't my idea of how I wish to win.
I will have to make a decision,
but I don't wish to move.
- Right.
- I believe...
this is a punishment
that I have brought upon myself...
for my bad decision-making.
- Do as you wish.
- You get what I'm saying, right?
- It's up to you to decide.
- Right.
You saved me once.
It broke my heart to see you wither away.
That was why I wished to save you as well.
Things are clearer for me now.
I won't wither away now.
I feel better now.
- That's a relief.
- Right.
If you have a change of heart,
- make sure to let me know.
- Right.
Luna seemed to have
a greater affection toward Team Gold.
She wished to end the game
as a Team Gold member.
I still didn't give up on her.
I couldn't leave her out.
Do you still have more to talk about?
- Well,
- We're done.
- I've shared my thoughts.
- Right. I'll think about it.
- We'll end here.
- Right.
- Thank you for coming.
- Thank you.
We should've talked sooner like this.
- Right. This is such a great sight...
- What a bummer.
- even when we're against each other.
- We should've gone to see you guys.
- We lacked communication.
- Right.
Feel free to ring the bell at any time.
- Knock at our door.
- Okay.
- We'll be waiting.
- Thank you.
Bye. Get some rest.
- I've shared my thoughts.
- What did you say?
- Did you ask if she wanted to return?
- Yes.
What did she say?
- She said she'll think about it.
- Right.
- She'll have to think carefully.
- They mentioned this as well.
No matter what happens,
they wanted us to save Luna...
- based on humanitarian considerations.
- Right.
- But they didn't tell Luna about this.
- I think everyone feels pity toward Luna.
- Right.
They suggested that...
- we take Luna back.
- Right.
So what's their stance right now?
"Come to Team Gold?"
They will sacrifice
some of their members as well.
But in this situation,
Team White and Team Red can't break up.
- That isn't possible.
- Right.
Should we meet Maillard?
Sounds good.
- My gosh!
- Yes?
We weren't able to see you today.
- We've had our talks.
- Did you talk to them?
- We've talked to them.
- Right.
- We talked with Team Gold.
- As you would have expected...
- What did you talk about with them?
- Well...
- They came to us first.
Team Gold came to see me in the morning.
- Simply put,
- Okay.
- they want us to move to their team.
So I asked, "What's good about that?"
And they said, "Team Black and Team Blue
will be punished,"
"and the rest will share the prize money
with gold."
That's because gold is spread out
right now.
So with the idea of serving justice,
- They wish to...
- they wish to make a way for themselves.
- Right.
- I believe that's a good move.
But I don't think I'll be accepting that.
Right.
It's our eighth day.
This isn't a time for harmony.
Team Gold was slow
with all of their decisions.
Tomorrow is the last day.
And as for Luna,
- We'll wait for Luna.
- we'll try to persuade her.
If war is declared today,
it will be by Team Blue.
If Team White does not wish
to join the fight,
- Team Red will.
- Right.
You don't have to spend anything...
or do anything.
This is a decision Leia should make.
This is why Team Blue must declare war.
Next morning,
we might be able to make a vote...
with the same number of lives
and credits...
as the number of members.
Right.
Out of the resources we are producing,
the hardest ones to produce are lives.
When the final vote happens,
we each might need one life
to make a vote.
In any way possible,
lives can become a variable
at the very last moment.
My final plan is to...
have more lives than gold.
This is why the resources...
- must be distributed like this.
- Right.
Team Red must have eight lives left.
Team Blue must have 4 lives left.
Team White must have 6 lives left.
- This is why.
- Why must Team Blue have four left?
We lose half of what we have
when we lose at war.
- One must be spent.
- Right.
(Four lives are required
while considering the spoils.)
We have issued 100 million diamonds
so far.
Around 25,000 dollars worth of diamonds...
were spent on weapons of war.
The weapon dealer
and the ally of the weapon dealer...
each have 12,500 dollars.
The remaining 75,000 dollars
must be shared.
When divided by six,
it's 12,500 dollars.
Excluding Donkey,
it's 37,500 dollars for the 3 in Team Red.
As for Team Blue,
it's 12,500 dollars for Pitou.
As for Team White,
it's 25,000 dollars for 2.
That's the overall plan.
So you'll work on this
when trading begins.
- I'll work on this when trading begins.
- Right.
The bomb will be used after that.
Let's not use the bomb.
We have to save our credits.
- That was included as well.
After using the bomb, we'll declare war.
But do we really have to go to war?
We must go to war.
- It's inevitable for us.
- Right.
Team Red shared that...
they were going to use the bomb,
which is their skill.
As a comparison to our history,
it's some sort of nuclear bomb.
It has the effect of blocking resistance.
I wondered if that was really necessary.
And if the bomb were to be used,
I wondered if going to war was necessary.
We were already in a very good position.
It made me think that going to war
was to fill the last one percent...
of the 99 percent we already had.
What play can Team Gold make?
- Hey!
- How did it go?
- We didn't do great.
- Right.
- To our disappointment...
- We missed a lot of them.
I heard the clapping three times.
You heard the clapping?
- It looks like they're acting.
- I heard clapping.
It seems like they produced a lot.
The production efficiency was really low.
- So how many did you produce?
- Should we tell you...
- how many questions we answered?
- Yes.
- Five?
- We...
We answered eight questions.
(Team Production did a great job.)
- Gosh!
- Siseon carried us today.
- Really?
That's our man!
We got our job done.
- Maillard will get things sorted for us.
- You still have more to do.
- What?
- There's a mission.
- Me?
You are today's warlord.
Gosh! You have to try going to war!
You have to declare war at this point.
That is why your diamonds
will be taken from you for now.
Understood.
But do you know what the problem is?
The Platform won't open tomorrow.
- The Community will close.
- Today will be the final count.
We should forget about tomorrow...
- and end things today.
- Right.
So we have to get
the calculations done today...
- Right.
- with the numbers.
- Except for those.
- Right.
How should we relocate ourselves?
- Team White should have a few members.
- We have to think about...
where we will relocate and become allies.
As of right now, the ones in Team White...
will be Paul and Leia.
If they are to have someone else,
- it will be Luna. That's it for them.
- Right.
The ones left in Team Red...
- will be like this.
- Right.
Team Blue will be like this.
- It will change...
- If she decides to move.
- based on Luna's decision.
- Right.
For your information,
Team Gold said this in the morning.
They made an offer to go with gold,
as they will make a few sacrifices.
- I will refuse their offer.
- Right.
That's it.
Changing the currency to gold...
- doesn't make sense.
- Right.
There's a trade ban,
so the gold cannot be distributed.
- Right. There's a trade ban.
- It's just the gold we have.
And to distribute gold,
credits must be spent...
- during each trade.
- Right.
- We're very short...
- It's hard to maintain the balance.
on credits to be able to do that.
- There's no way to distribute gold.
- Right.
All possibilities were closed down.
We stopped them from doing anything.
- It's suffocating for them.
- We stopped them from doing anything.
As they might find a way...
- to shake us up,
- Right.
I gave them a trade ban
to secure a complete victory.
I'm here to collect
the produced resources.
(Team Blue's produced resource)
(Team Blue's produced resource: 8 lives)
I'm rich.
Goodbye.
(Resources After Day 8's Production)
(Team Blue:
12,500,000 diamonds, 16 credits)
(Team Blue: 8 lives)
(Resources After Day 8's Production)
(Relocation request)
- I will return to Red.
- I request a relocation.
- Will you accept it?
- I accept it.
Let's go and eat.
Okay.
- Are you drawing again?
- Yes.
(Maillard plans for a resource move
ahead of a 3rd war.)
It's the trading session
in the afternoon after lunch, right?
Yes.
- We can't trade.
- Right.
- Should we go and watch?
- We'll go and watch.
- Right.
- Let's watch how they move...
and try to make them come to us.
There's a lot of lobbying
in the real world.
- Right.
- It's not just presidents talking.
- It could be international organizations.
- It could be business people.
- Right.
We should make an appeal
with different points of view.
Many of the decisions haven't been made...
just on the expected value.
We should belatedly acknowledge
that we didn't get ourselves involved...
and try to make ourselves work with them.
The weather is great.
- Right.
- It's in use.
Where?
Isn't that where the resources
are collected?
- The produced resources?
- Right.
Does it take that long?
I'm not sure.
(Vector is setting
the war and weapon costs.)
The war cost will be set
to zero diamonds and zero gold.
The war cost has been set.
I will announce the weapon cost.
It will be set to zero diamonds...
and zero gold.
The weapon cost has been set.
The members
of the diamond alliance became one.
For them to share resources freely,
declare war to their advantage,
and avoid the most damage,
a weapon cost can't be set.
That was why I set everything to zero.
(Lunchtime)
I think it will be neat to tell you now.
I gave it some thought.
I think it will be hard
to accept your offer.
- Right.
- All right.
For me to make this decision,
my team members have to go.
I couldn't reach an agreement
with my team members.
I thought it would be fair...
- to tell you as soon as possible.
- Right.
That's the reason...
- I'm telling you now.
- Right.
We've done everything we could.
We have to think of the next step.
I asked if you had a different plan.
- We have to think of one.
- I hope you can find a good way.
I hoped they had a different plan.
If this was their one and only plan,
I just broke it apart.
That was when I thought...
war would be their last resort.
Your special meal has arrived.
It's our last lunch today.
Should we eat together?
- We can share.
- I'm fine with that as well.
- We can all share.
- Right.
(Team Gold joins in for lunch today.)
It's curry.
Being in an actual conversation
with the others...
is the best way to fit into a community.
- Enjoy your meal.
Enjoy your meal.
Why are you called Pitou?
It's from an animated series
called "Hunter x Hunter."
I watched "Hunter x Hunter."
Which character is that?
It's 1 of the 3 strongest Chimera Ants
toward the end.
Does Vector have to do with direction?
- Yes. It has to do with decisions and...
- It's similar to Ugong.
Ugong resembles direction as well.
Consistently going in one direction.
Why are you Mokgye? I heard
a brief explanation of it yesterday.
There's a four-character idiom
called "Mokgyejideok."
It's the state of being calm
in any situation,
looking like a chicken made of wood.
It's about keeping calm, right?
- Right.
- But you were shaken a lot yesterday.
- It's a goal.
- Why would you say that?
I was just trying to break the ice.
- Breaking the ice on the last day?
- Right.
- On the last day.
- This is the only chance.
- Breaking the ice.
- Right.
The atmosphere was great during lunch.
Team Gold joined in for lunch as well.
It felt like we finally had a proper meal.
I realized that they wanted to
play the game with genuine hearts,
but it took them too long to adapt.
Seeing the way they behaved
in the Town Hall...
and the way they came to us...
to talk to us...
made me want to stop declaring war
from an emotional perspective.
This sort of gathering...
should have happened days ago.
Transfer students always struggle.
That's how it is.
Everyone else was good friends,
but new transfer students came.
"Hi. We're smart and rich."
"Would you like to be our friends?"
If they go like this,
anyone would go, "That's rude."
No one would say, "Sure!"
I know because
I've transferred schools a lot.
I went to five different
elementary schools.
That was why it became
a lot more complicated for me.
"Why behave this way now?"
"We're planning other things right now."
I knew that sitting and laughing
with each other...
was a temporary moment of peace.
I sat with them
and left out of frustration.
(Luna approaches Leia.)
- This is a personal thing.
- Right.
I'm so annoyed with Team Black
and Team Blue.
Unlike us, other teams...
seem indebted to those
who sacrificed themselves...
for the game.
Meanwhile, the enemy is the one...
who caused unnecessary sacrifices.
Team Blue is the one
that suddenly started a war,
and the ones who were sacrificed
were Hamlet, Boss, Genie, and Salt.
However, people don't seem
to think about...
who forced them out of the compound.
For instance,
Team Blue had a lot of lives to spare,
and Team Black was the weapon dealer.
After the revelation,
their anger should've been channeled...
in the same direction as mine.
I didn't get why everyone else wasn't
as furious with them as I was.
The ones I'm upset with...
aren't Team White or Team Red,
who are allied with them.
(Luna, Influencer)
It's Team Blue and Team Black
I'm mostly mad at.
I'm not asking everyone to be
on the same page,
but I still want confirmation.
You don't think that, right?
Am I annoyed with them?
Yes.
- But am I going to...
- Do something about it?
I must keep my team alive,
but achieving my goal
without excluding them...
won't be easy.
That's why I'm in this position.
That's why we started a war yesterday.
Let's say Siseon and Paul
joined Team Gold.
The team will have six people.
Including you, that will be seven votes.
If that happens, we'll get rid
of Red, Donkey, Black, and Blue.
But you don't hate them enough to do that.
We have too much history with Red.
- It's not that simple for you.
- Yes.
Why don't you join our team instead?
- Then...
- I...
don't want to share a prize with them.
I'd rather not win anything
than share a prize with Blue and Black.
That's how much I dislike them right now.
I see.
Let's take this back and talk some more.
Stay here. I'll be right back.
Who said they wanted hot dogs earlier?
- I want one.
- Me.
You're deciding...
- with your emotions right now.
- Yes.
We only joined forces with Team Red
because we have a common goal.
Maillard's only goal...
- is his team's survival.
- Right.
But Donkey's on that team too.
- That ties them to Black.
- Yes.
I've already accepted that
and given up on teaming up with them.
Right.
I don't want to share a prize with them.
I'd rather not switch teams.
That's my choice,
and I figured I should tell you that.
I believe we resemble each other a bit,
so if I were in your position right now,
I'd make the same choice.
- Right.
That's why I want to respect your choice.
However,
although I'm with you emotionally,
I hope you know
I made a different choice...
because I'm choosing
as a member of a team,
not just for myself.
Had I been in your shoes,
I would've made the same decision.
- Right.
- I feel the same way.
Good.
We're in different positions now.
- We are.
- Right.
Still, you can always come to me to talk.
Got it.
- Okay.
- Off we go.
- What's in here?
- I put everything in here.
Lives too?
- Yes, 14 lives.
- Right.
There are some vouchers and the stamp.
Can't we carry them in our pockets?
- Are you afraid we'd lose these?
- To hide that we want to trade.
Oh, that. I see.
Can't we hide our intentions a bit?
(They carry the resources
in their pockets instead.)
- I can carry some more.
- No, I'm good.
- We're all set.
- Let's go.
Are we good?
- Do you have the stamp?
- Yes.
Off we go.
- I see you're already eating.
- Join us, guys.
- In the end, we...
- But...
(They see Leia talking to Luna.)
- I'm off.
- Okay.
- Isn't Luna going to join us?
- I think she's out.
- She'll choose not to join us?
- Yes.
I think she's just going to go out
with the rest of Team Gold.
We all have different opinions on things.
Not everyone thinks the same way.
That goes without saying, I suppose.
People...
I wonder what this is about.
This is an announcement
from the Community Center.
The trading for Day Eight will begin.
Please note that due to an agreement...
between the leaders,
Team Gold can't use the Trading Station.
Please keep this in mind.
Today's war cost...
(Today's war cost...)
is 0 diamonds and 0 gold.
(Today's war cost: 0 diamonds, 0 gold)
This concludes the announcement
from the Community Center.
They dropped bad news...
- when we were in a good mood.
- Well,
that certainly ruined the mood.
The next keyword,
"What's a rut or a slump?"
- You're hooked, aren't you?
- A rut or a slump.
I only thought of polyamory
because of that relationship rut.
But that's impossible, right?
- Exactly.
- It's the same with friends.
Some friends are great company
when out shopping,
- You're right.
- while others aren't.
Like that,
some spouses give emotional support,
while others are good for only one thing.
Some spouses help you grow as a person...
- True.
- and open up new doors for your career.
Let's say you're dating someone who's...
Lunchtime was
the most anxious part of my day today.
To adjust our resources ahead of the war,
at least 12 trades needed to take place
at the Platform.
(Maillard, Cooking YouTuber)
But that takes quite a long time.
But with Team Gold already having a spot
at the Platform,
they could see trades taking place.
Anyone could tell
that the trading itself looked suspicious.
Had Team Gold noticed
something suspicious...
and headed straight
to the Community Center...
to wage war on any team here,
it would've posed a massive threat
to our alliance.
That's why that moment was
the most nerve-wracking for me.
I value my personal relationships.
- You know why?
- That's what I said.
- Doing this...
- Different, right?
Seriously?
The situation here
is very similar to an actual war.
One hour into the trading session.
Today was practically
the last day we could trade...
since a war will stop all transactions.
That's why before the war, we needed...
to balance the diamonds, credits,
and lives everyone needed to survive,
but Team Gold wouldn't leave
the Town Hall.
We didn't know when to make the trade.
As a person...
("We need to talk to Blue outside.")
- So...
- Hold on.
- I get that, but...
- Right?
By doing that...
What do you think?
I think Luna will just be on the outside.
- From this plan?
- Yes.
Luna's made up her mind
to go out with the rest of Team Gold.
- So, as it is...
- I see.
I get that, but when do we trade?
What if Team Gold won't leave?
Maillard said we needed to talk
to Blue outside.
- They're not thinking about leaving.
- Exactly.
This morning, they said
they weren't going to start a war.
- Then...
- I'm not sure about that.
- Even after saying that...
- That's why I'm hovering like this.
I'm holding my ground.
If Team Gold makes a move,
- I'm going to block them first.
- How can we trade...
when they're here?
- That's what I'm saying.
- Just...
Can't we just go ahead with the trade?
We obviously just need to get it done,
but we'll have to talk to Maillard first.
You should step outside for a bit.
Did you bring your resources?
- The credits and stuff?
- Yes, I have mine.
We need to trade, but they're not leaving.
We should just do it with them here.
They don't intend to start a war.
- Really?
- You can...
distribute the resources
and set off the bomb...
- to destroy lives.
- Right.
If they see red and start a war,
we can absorb their attack...
- and strike back.
- Sure.
They could pretend to go back
after making us lower our guard,
and then head over there instead.
You never know.
Why on earth are they still here?
They really don't intend to start a war.
That isn't entirely far-fetched.
That's how Team Gold operates.
- Is he the leader?
- No.
He's not, right?
- Mokgye's the leader.
- Right.
Mokgye keeps looking this way.
Mokgye has been looking our way.
- I'm the only one who's anxious.
- I know.
I have over ten trades...
- to get done today.
- Exactly.
He needs to get through all of them,
and fast.
It could be like this.
They could be waiting for us to trade,
and the moment they see it happening,
they could make their move.
Are you slightly bored?
I wanted to hear what people had to say,
and maybe our activities...
To be honest,
I feel like we're finally meeting...
- face-to-face.
- I know.
It's like we've been behind
closed doors up until now,
- and finally...
- After four days, right?
We're finally meeting face-to-face
and actually talking.
- We're talking now.
- I've finally been able...
- I know.
- to talk to everyone.
"Are people finally
coming up to me to talk?"
That's what I'm thinking now.
I'm finally able to talk to people
outside my team.
- Finally,
- Together...
we feel like you've accepted us,
which is nice.
I know.
You said that your wish...
- was to talk to everyone here.
- Seriously.
- What a good feeling.
- Talk away.
- Darn.
- I mean it.
- Together, right?
- I haven't been able to even talk to you,
and it came down to this.
- True.
- When the timing isn't right,
- there's nothing you can do.
- Sure.
I guess we should've
taken action a day or two earlier.
- True.
- Right.
I totally agree.
Should we just do it?
Maillard, maybe the leaders...
- should gather.
- Yes.
Should the leaders talk at lunchtime too?
Yes.
Am I invited too?
Well, that's...
We should limit it to those
who can use the Platform for now.
We need to trade our resources, you see.
I need to purchase lives.
Yes.
- I figured you'd need lives.
- True.
We should talk for a bit.
We should transfer the lives we got.
Distribute them, I mean.
- I'll clear out.
- Sure.
- I feel bad for her.
- Leia should be here.
Leia? I'll bring her over.
- We need to tail her.
- Right.
I've written down what we should trade.
If I give you this and our resources,
can you take care of all the trades?
- You need to hand over the resources.
- Right.
- Okay.
- We should trade.
- That's right.
- In total...
- Just follow it exactly.
To execute the plan
we put together to perfection,
the resources have to change hands
without Team Gold finding out.
But Team Gold was occupying the Platform.
That's why I brought
the leaders together...
to move forward with the trade...
and trigger the war.
White, Blue, Red, and Black.
- Diamonds, life, and credit.
- Life and credit.
How many credits should I trade
and how many should I keep?
For the Platform to operate,
a direct exchange won't do.
I need to sell what I have,
buy what I need,
sell it to someone else,
and buy from them.
To set it at 50 million,
you need to give me 12.5 million diamonds.
Since the process is pretty complicated,
I just asked Maillard
for the final numbers.
With the Platform officially open,
I passed along the skill I was holding...
to Team Red.
- Is it Day Eight today?
- Yes.
This expires after Day Eight.
(Black sells Bomb Manufacturing License
to Red for 1 diamond.)
- Here.
- Darn.
(Platform Trade Summary:
White, Blue, Red, Black)
(Diamonds, Lives, Credits, Gold)
(Declaring war)
Good job, guys.
What if they make us lower our guard...
and strike Red or White?
If they do that, we'll just have to win.
- You never know.
- You're right.
I want to be safe.
You are. There's no need to worry.
- You're not safe.
- Here.
I'll be safe if they strike me,
but that's unlikely.
Exactly. Yes, that.
- It'll be a disaster if they hit red.
- Right.
We'd lose 25,000 dollars.
There wasn't a single moment
where I could lower my guard.
We didn't have that kind of luxury.
If Mokgye ever left the Platform,
I had to sprint to ensure
I reached the Community Center first.
That was how critical my situation was.
That's why I kept my eyes
on everything and everyone.
I checked Mokgye's position
and was wary of her movements.
We had a plan for today too.
We couldn't risk Team Gold discovering...
the trade taking place at the Platform...
or letting them declare war...
before we had time to react,
so it was my job to keep them...
engaged and occupied.
That's why I brought up various topics
to keep their attention focused on me.
I'm not at all curious about the past.
- Two hours into the trading session.
- Time flies when we're talking like this.
- I know.
- Has no one traded?
- You're here, so you haven't.
- They're trading right now.
We can't be a part of it though.
This is when I feel the most anxious...
and on edge.
If we're being honest,
we're currently ahead.
Circumstantially, I mean.
However,
I'm the most on edge.
I think...
that's because you have it
in your heart to win for sure...
and not halfheartedly.
That's true. You see,
up until Day Five,
I just loved the quizzes,
and I was having a blast.
Ever since that day,
it's been a real struggle and so draining.
Don't you think you had to fight
an unseen threat?
There wasn't anyone
who was actually a threat to us.
Even if there's no clear justification,
a clear victory might be of value.
In my case,
the only objective in my mind
is the survival of my teammates.
Either way, the reality check is real.
I absolutely agree.
What are we even fighting for?
We'll have to go to war soon,
and honestly,
it takes a heavy mental toll on me.
We can't avoid it, though, right?
Can you walk away from it?
It's like this. I mean,
it sounds a bit funny...
comparing it to the arms race
between the US and the Soviets,
but I fear I might be the target if not.
It's just like
the US and Cuba wondering...
which side is going to press
the nuclear button first.
Wait. Can you two...
I'm just afraid
someone will target me first.
- No one's a threat, but...
- Team Gold doesn't have that in mind.
No one's actively targeting me, but...
Are you going to activate your skill first
or declare war first?
The skill.
Going nuclear in this situation?
If you're going to use the skill,
you have to get moving.
- We'll go together.
- Sure.
I'll close the Platform then.
- I'm going right now.
- I'm going.
- Right now?
- Yes.
Let's go together.
- Are you going over there?
- Yes.
Okay.
It was hard to watch.
We were talking friendly
with them one minute,
only to wage war the next.
I wouldn't have made it
if I were on the other end of that.
(Leia, Journalist)
That's why I asked Maillard...
if this war was absolutely necessary.
At that moment,
even Maillard was sick of it too.
"Was it necessary to finish them off?"
But in Maillard's case,
he had already done the math.
This was necessary
to guarantee everyone's safety.
I thought it wouldn't hurt
to give the others a chance,
but if that decision...
was going to compromise our safety,
I couldn't bring myself
to stand in the way.
And not actively stopping that decision...
was my unspoken way of giving consent.
The guilt that I had was mine to carry.
In the end, my decision...
aligned with the group's.
I'm not the only one here who's nervous.
How so?
I'm still not safe.
- Because they might target you?
- Yes.
You lose 25,000 dollars.
"Should I start a war?"
"Would they start a war?"
"Is someone targeting me? Them?"
"We aren't thinking of firing,
but are they?"
- "Shouldn't we strike first?"
- Right.
Let's quickly get over there
and get it done.
Are you going to use the skill first?
That'll blow up three lives, right?
- That's right.
- Yes.
We'll also use ten credits.
- We're using everything we can.
- We're so nasty.
Unbelievable.
Let's wait here.
I don't even know
if this is right anymore.
Seriously.
Those residents found happiness here
for the first time,
but I'm going nuclear to drive them out.
Please state the reason for your visit.
I'll use the Bomb Manufacturing License.
Team Red has activated its skill.
From now on, Team Red may use its skill.
You become more dependent and...
So that's why!
I heard kids these days...
- Team Red has activated a skill.
- Red?
Team Red can now use their skill.
- Red's skill is reducing lives.
- Right.
Yes, that happened.
- Our lives?
- Yes.
It's for the benefit of everyone.
How does it benefit everyone?
How many lives will be reduced?
Three lives will be reduced.
When it was announced
that the skill was activated,
we were obviously the target.
The first thing that came to mind was,
"Why go this far?"
I felt that they did that to eliminate...
any chance of us winning.
They would want to stop us.
They'd be really disappointed...
when they suddenly lose at the end...
after almost winning.
Up until then, I even thought
that it was a decision...
I would have also made in their shoes.
- Shall we talk for a while?
- Let's do that.
- This place is...
- Shall we go upstairs?
We can leave.
Submit ten credits...
to receive a bomb.
We made up our minds.
We have no choice but to go to war.
The key is which team has the lives.
They probably put all the lives...
in one place, right?
They probably gave them to Black.
They may have given them to Black.
But anyway, we have no choice
but to go to war.
Now I think it all comes down...
to who we put our bet on.
Even if we start a war,
- can we actually gain any lives from it?
- Right.
So who should we wage war against?
Where could the lives be?
We have to think about where they are.
Wouldn't they be with Blue?
Please collect the bomb
from the central box.
I'll use the bomb.
Please choose the team
you would like to use the bomb on.
Team Gold.
Which team has the most members?
They started a war first.
- What is this?
- Maybe...
We have to quickly...
- Anyway, we...
- Team Red has used their bomb...
- on Team Gold.
- Two of them...
Three of Team Gold's lives
have been destroyed.
Gold Team's leader,
please visit the Community Center...
and surrender three lives.
Okay, then...
Shall we talk as we head there?
- This side...
- But...
I think we'll need to hurry...
I don't think we have...
- Much time?
- much time for this.
They started a war first.
The team with no lives would start a war.
Right. Let's just start a war on any team.
I can just say, "I declare war."
It can't be helped.
How do you declare war?
- We can just go and...
- Wait, what...
- Let's go this way.
- Let's talk on the way.
What do you think?
- Do they have one life left?
- Yes.
Is it foolish...
to declare war in advance?
It could have ended like this, actually.
Honestly, I don't want to go to war.
Why are you disappointed, Leia?
I really don't want...
to fight a war without justification.
Why is there no justification?
What justification is there?
To reduce the risks.
The risks were already reduced.
To reduce it to a minimum.
This isn't reducing it to a minimum.
It's just wiping it out completely.
Right. Reducing it to a minimum.
But I think we can win
without going that far.
- Actually...
- This...
- is a nuclear bomb.
- Right.
- This should be enough.
- That should be enough.
Stopping here is actually more cruel.
- Right.
- What are they supposed to do?
- Do nothing?
- It just means three of them are out.
- It's just saying, "Just leave."
- If we go to war,
- they'll...
- It's our mercy.
Then I think it would be right
to at least let them declare the war.
Then...
- it becomes a guessing game.
- Since they wouldn't know who to choose?
So...
After talking it through,
I'm getting to think,
"Goodness."
We're all in the same position.
Use the skill and start the war.
Honestly, I don't want to do it today.
Go.
- Start the war.
- Do it quickly.
Let's hear from them first.
- It's to eliminate every variable.
- They did it to do that.
Even if we survive the war...
Let's hear from them first.
Can I go in?
- They're...
- It's finished now.
Do it quickly.
Please state the purpose of your visit.
I declare war.
Please state the target group
you wish to declare war on.
Team Gold.
Team Blue has declared war on Team Gold.
Today's war cost...
is 0 diamonds and 0 gold.
It's a bit cruel, though.
The war cost has been paid.
Why did you do that?
A nuclear bomb?
That's how it is.
I need...
our alliance to win.
I have to use all the means I can.
Is it a war?
Did they start a war?
- If this doesn't work, we fail as well.
- They declared war as well.
- They declared...
- Team Blue...
has declared war on Team Gold.
- Yes.
- Okay.
This was a decision I had to make.
You didn't have to go this far.
I had to.
Actually, we were thinking,
- "Let's just wait and see for now."
- Yes.
I was curious
about the worst-case scenario.
I did feel like we might be going
a little too far...
against the weaker team.
Honestly, even blocking...
the sanction...
(Reboot opposed the no-war treaty.)
made me really uneasy.
I thought Team Gold...
was still capable of doing something.
Honestly, you're all players...
capable of making great plays.
I was very nervous.
I tried to make the best move I could.
I really used every skill we had.
The reason we're going this far...
is because I feel very anxious.
- We're left with one life now.
- Yes.
Why do we have to win...
the war?
If you win, more members can survive.
- Survive?
- Yes.
Even if we lose the war,
we'll have one person left,
- and if we win, we'll have 2 or 3.
- Right.
Having 2 or 3 people survive...
would be meaningless for us.
It's already meaningless.
It feels like you declared another war...
like you were wiping out cockroaches.
Did you start a war first...
- because you thought we'd start one?
- That's right.
Honestly,
- we don't want to fight this war.
- I understand.
If you hadn't gone to war today,
were you just planning
to spend the day chatting?
We'd start a war
if we had anything to benefit from it.
We get nothing from it.
Why would we want to chat...
- without going to war?
- We...
We declared the war
to protect our resources.
Forget it. All right. Let's just go.
The siren sounded again,
and a war was declared.
I really wanted to confront them about it.
I lost my temper at that moment.
"Why do we have to go to war?"
We had already lost.
Having 1 life or 0
makes no difference to us.
But they said it
like they were giving us a chance.
"You'd be able to get some lives
if you win."
"You should do your best until the end."
To me,
that felt like,
"Make our victory more interesting."
And with things getting to this point,
I'm basically going in...
with nothing I can do.
"What's the reason for starting a war?"
"Wasn't it the team with zero lives
that started the war?"
They said,
"You'll get 1 or 2 lives if you win."
I found that really insulting.
That means
they already set the number of lives.
They wanted to start a war...
from that position.
It felt very cruel.
"Why are they doing this?"
"Did they really lose their minds?"
I couldn't understand them.
How could no one see...
that it was a bit strange?
If you think about it,
if it had ended with us
using the bomb earlier,
you may not have anything else you can do.
I didn't think they'd go this far.
It feels so inhumane.
Isn't it a bit scary?
It was kind of creepy...
how they smiled like that...
after planning all of this.
Their two-faced side was really scary.
They're all crazy.
- We have to end it...
- So I can clearly see...
your determination to move forward...
- It was out of our greed as well.
- without leaving anything to chance.
- But that...
- Let's...
Let's go up and have a talk
among ourselves as well, Ugong.
- Okay.
- Let's talk first.
- Let's go up.
- All right.
- Luna went up.
- She did?
We've entered a state of war.
All residents, please remain
in your dormitories.
Since they're saying...
all that,
it doesn't feel good.
- I'm against fighting back.
- What?
- You're against entering the war?
- Yes.
- That's...
- Why?
- It's pointless.
- what I'm thinking as well.
Wouldn't it be fun?
- No, but...
- It's not about the fun.
I don't want us to be their toy.
- We'll consider it a loss.
- Let's just go home.
- That sounds good.
I really think it's an unnecessary war.
Me too.
It wasn't necessary.
They started a war
because they were anxious.
I understand Maillard's standards.
"It's not right to leave
even the slightest possibility open."
But...
But judging from their attitudes,
they never thought about going to war.
I totally agree with that.
The bomb? I agree.
They could have stopped there.
- That's what I think.
- They're saying that's more hypocritical.
- That it's crueler. But...
- Right.
But that's...
a bit of a stretch.
They had no intention
of going to war anyway.
We couldn't stop them...
In fact, we joined them.
Right.
We could have blocked them
with our bodies...
if they were going to enter
to start the war.
It wouldn't have been too late
to do it then.
It was too rash.
Well...
What should I say?
Let's not cry.
Yes.
This is what I'm mad about.
I wouldn't have minded...
if we could all survive when we win.
"One of you should leave."
That also doesn't make sense.
There's one thing I regret.
Things would have been neat...
if we had just accepted it...
when they asked.
It was our mistake for not doing that.
We were always one step behind too.
But there was a reason
we were always a step behind.
- Right.
- We came later.
- Right. Yes.
- We had to figure out the situation...
- with limited information.
- Of course.
The rules and the situation here...
We had to figure out
people's personalities.
- So...
- Everything was...
we could only follow along
with their decisions...
while guessing from the outside,
- honestly speaking.
- Right.
About issues like Donkey's.
They never told us.
- Right.
- We could have done something...
if they told us things
because they wanted something.
I'm glad we came as the catfish.
That says how good we are.
As expected.
That's a compliment.
They overprepared like that...
because we looked strong,
so they were trying to defend themselves.
They kept asking what skills we had.
- They think we're hiding something. Yes.
- They kept thinking that.
That's why they kept trying
to eliminate us...
and tried not to leave any chances.
I can understand them, though.
It's disappointing in many ways,
but we did really well.
Let's consider this a good experience.
- Let's keep it neat.
- Right.
Let's not leave while they mock us.
I want us to leave...
after declaring defeat.
I think that's the best we can do.
Declaring defeat.
That alone can say...
what a terrible thing they did...
and how they crushed our spirit.
They can think about that.
In the end...
Well...
We don't have lives,
and we have to go home today.
But one of us has no other choice...
than to stay here.
I want to take responsibility...
as the leader...
and stay behind to vote.
I think
if the original, new Gold member...
stays here until the end,
they'll think they won.
But if I stay behind...
I was an original member as well.
I would stay here until the end,
but I would be the only one leaving
with no prize.
I think we need to show them that...
so they could think...
- about what they did.
- But...
honestly speaking,
it breaks my heart
to leave behind our youngest member.
And from a humanitarian perspective,
that's an incredibly irresponsible thing
for adults to do.
- So...
- I'm saying,
if one person has to stay behind,
that has to be me.
- Right. That's a bit...
- Since I'm an original member.
"What did you do?"
"You teamed up with the original members,"
"but in the end, you singled out
one of the original members."
That's the message I want to send.
So will you stay behind?
- Can you do that?
- Okay.
- Yes.
- We'll exit.
So, this...
shakes your identity.
Right.
You'll get the thought,
"Am I really the villain?"
"Am I being rejected
because I'm the villain..."
"and I did bad things?"
Your identity gets shaken.
Your sense of identity.
There's nothing you can do to solve that,
but you keep...
having to clear up misunderstandings
and resolve things.
You keep getting discouraged,
so you end up giving up.
We didn't live our lives
based on other people's opinions so far.
The way I see myself. That...
was the standard.
But that's shaking.
That was hard.
But I really enjoyed being with you.
It was nice.
I didn't come here for this.
Ugong said he felt like
this wasn't the fight he had in mind.
He thought we were fighting
a different battle.
I agreed with him.
I think the reason I came
to that realization as late as I did...
was because
I was one of the original members.
So I could understand
why they made the decisions they did.
I could have done the same thing...
in their shoes.
While listening to Ugong,
I could really understand
how frustrating and hard...
it would have been
to be rejected as enemies...
just because we joined later...
when I put myself in their shoes.
I just felt sorry.
I felt bad.
(Luna, Influencer)
So we didn't want...
to let them have the satisfaction...
of winning a pointless war
until the very end.
We decided to declare defeat today.
Team Gold is heading down.
Why?
They're heading down with their resources.
What?
What's going on?
What are they doing as a group?
Where are they going?
What's going on?
Declaring defeat?
What?
Aren't they declaring defeat?
- That's Luna.
- Right.
Right.
Get in there and do your thing, Mokgye.
We declare defeat in this war.
(Team Blue has declared war on Team Gold.)
The declaration of defeat
has been confirmed.
Team Blue has won the war.
Please submit your spoils into the slot.
It's here.
(Transfer of spoils)
The spoils have been
successfully submitted.
Please select the final survivor.
The final survivor...
is Luna.
Team Gold's final survivor
has been chosen.
You may now exit.
- Are you done?
- I'm done.
- Good job.
- I made Luna the final survivor.
- Thank you.
- Please do well until the end.
- Okay.
- Our mom.
- It'll be painful for just one more day.
- Right.
- I'll do my best.
- Good luck.
- Let's go. Good work, everyone.
- Let's go.
- Good work, everyone.
I'm so sad.
(Team Gold's Mokgye, Ugong, Maetel
leave the town.)
This is an announcement
from the Community Center.
Due to Team Gold's declaration of defeat,
Team Blue has won the war.
Effective immediately,
the state of war has been lifted.
Oh, I'm stressed.
All functions of the Community Town
are back to normal.
Effective immediately,
- the state of war has been lifted.
- Oh, my gosh.
All functions of the Community Town...
- are back to normal.
- Oh, my gosh.
This is the worst.
So they're all going home except one.
They're saying they can't handle a war.
Well...
- I can understand.
- Right.
We pushed them into a corner.
We did try to hit them again
when they were already...
pushed into a corner and down.
- But why?
- Team Blue...
has won the war.
Leader of Team Blue,
please collect the spoils from the Center.
The spoils have been collected.
This doesn't feel right.
(Team Blue collects the spoils.)
It feels a bit anticlimactic.
It feels like I'm leaving...
without getting to do anything.
There are many moments I regret.
Actually, we had some chances,
but I don't think
we were able to act on those chances.
It's not easy to persuade people.
It's not easy to change the world.
I felt so once again.
I think I'll live with more respect
for those who create change.
Our smart Luna.
Do your best until the end.
You did so well. You were so cool.
Thank you.
It feels...
like I was just in my room
and didn't get to do much.
I'm kind of sad about that.
I think we had...
many members who thought things through...
and were careful about making decisions.
In a way, it could be
because we're all too smart.
We pictured the chessboards in our minds,
trying to find the correct answer.
I guess that took a long time.
But looking at this community...
In the end,
even when great ideas...
or legislation are brought forth,
people in society move...
depending on how something is marketed...
and how you sway public opinion
to present an idea.
I think, in a way,
we're leaving like this
because we're hoping...
people understand how we were thinking.
I should've communicated...
a bit faster and more proactively.
But I was so late. I regretted that a lot.
Would it have been better...
if I communicated more proactively?
Or would it not have made
much of a difference?
Many thoughts came up in my head.
There are many worlds I didn't know about.
I mean, I'm just a nerd.
But I guess being here was nice.
Yes, it was nice to get to talk...
to a diverse group of people.
(Leia, Paul)
(Pitou, Siseon, Donkey,
Maillard, Izaha, Vector)
(Maetel, Ugong, Mokgye)
(Luna)
- Can we have a quick chat, Luna?
- Sure.
Just a quick chat.
Can you tell me a bit
about how you made your decision?
Well, first...
We don't know why everyone is...
taking things this far.
We already knew we were going to lose.
Because our final strategy...
was to persuade White somehow.
Our defeat has already been decided.
So why did everyone keep attacking...
Right.
There was no reason to,
so why did everyone keep attacking us?
This is just ridicule at this point.
"If you win,
we'll give you one more life."
What nonsense.
We had no reason to fight,
so that's why we left.
There's nothing for us to gain
through war.
We didn't want a war.
Every time, someone else
has declared war on me.
Of course, maybe I was too late.
I could've started the war.
Maybe I was letting it happen.
Anyway, I don't like
having people declare war against me.
If there was even a small chance
that we could win the war,
I'd fight passionately.
That's what a player should do.
But it was already decided.
But everyone...
keeps acting like Gold is the enemy.
But Gold didn't do anything wrong.
If we did anything wrong,
it was that we didn't move quickly.
We may seem strong,
but everyone was struggling a lot.
You didn't let us do anything.
We tried to trade, but we couldn't.
We tried to form alliances,
but we couldn't.
You could say...
they were all strategic failures...
or mistakes in judgment.
So that's why I acknowledged all of that.
I accepted defeat.
I know those actions stemmed from fear.
I also know
those actions stemmed from concern.
But we didn't have the capacity
to be understanding of all of that.
We just...
kept getting beat down.
So everyone decided to leave.
But in any case,
one person has to stay.
I told them I wanted to do that.
I wanted to stay...
to show the original members...
that they didn't have to take things
this far.
Everyone is getting prize money except me.
I wanted to tell everyone that.
I completely understand.
First of all,
I'm so sorry.
About this situation.
I couldn't stop them.
White did join in.
I did join in.
Up until yesterday, yes,
the war was partially about survival.
But today's war,
being completely honest,
had no justification.
If there was a justification,
it was Maillard's judgment
that we needed...
to remove the last unforeseen risk.
Those repeated thoughts...
of mistrust of the other side...
made us want to be sure.
I still did think it was too cruel.
But at the bottom of it, you're right.
It was a war...
that left us with absolutely nothing.
My heart feels so heavy.
But surrendering...
is something that happens
in an actual war.
Also, Ugong strongly wanted
to declare defeat.
- You're right.
- It must've been frustrating.
- Of course.
Because things didn't go
the way they wanted.
I was with them for the first time.
They had lost all motivation
to start a war...
- by lunchtime.
- They lost their motivation.
Oh, gosh. It's a bit...
I agreed with using the bomb.
I agreed with blocking them
from doing anything with the bomb.
But...
I am thinking it was a bit rash.
We think,
"You had a chance,
but you turned it down."
But for them, they could think,
"We haven't been here for long,"
"and we had no information,"
"so we can't make that judgment."
"If you see things that way,"
"we feel wronged."
They could protest like that.
For example, if you look
at declaring defeat or surrender...
as an action you take...
to lessen the damages of war,
this doesn't have that benefit.
Because you lose resources all the same.
Exactly, it's the same amount of damage.
The fact
that they didn't even try to win...
- is regrettable.
- Right.
There's nothing we can do.
We can't fix that feeling
we have about each other.
My heart keeps going back and forth.
"I get it."
"But that was still not it."
- I keep going back and forth like that.
- I feel...
a bit bad, but I'm also mad.
There's nothing we can do.
How is Leia?
I'm worried about how she's feeling.
- She's completely out of it.
- Oh, no.
- Seriously.
- I'm going to go see Leia.
- Go ahead.
Okay.
A lot was said.
I said,
"I don't think a war is necessary."
"No, we need to make it clearer."
"And that's the polite thing to do."
Some people said that.
I don't know.
I'm sorry to say this,
but there was a lot
that could've been done.
For example, you could've tried
to appease them more...
before lunchtime.
"Give us a chance to buy weapons,
at least."
You could've done anything.
But this is what you did.
"Since we're obviously going to lose,
let's surrender."
"Let's ruin everything." Doing that...
I'm so sorry,
but I really think
that was rude to everyone.
You prevented us
from doing all of the things...
we tried to do in this game.
Isn't the reason you think
we didn't do our best...
that you didn't see
all of the things we tried to do?
- That could be the case.
- Yes.
- But...
- In the majority alliance,
you said some things happened.
There were some attempts at persuasion,
some failures, some reattempts.
- You said you tried many things.
- Yes.
But to us, it didn't seem like that.
To us, it was loosening up the game.
To us, that seemed rude.
That's a difference in perspective.
We each did our best...
- in the groups we were a part of.
- Fine.
So that's why we did that.
So if you say from a position of power,
"You could've begged more."
"You could've done this or that."
"You ran away without doing anything
like cowards."
If you say that...
That's too...
Too...
Don't you think that's too cruel?
- You're in such a superior position.
- You're right.
- But I really...
- You're part of such a majority.
You were never in the minority...
where you couldn't do anything.
That's not true.
I was White.
What did we try our best to do then?
Three of us died.
I even volunteered to die.
We accepted that result.
So are you saying, "We declared war,"
"and you didn't even try
to form an alliance..."
- You didn't even try to win.
- "or try to really fight?"
"You just left."
Are you blaming us for doing that?
I'm saying we're just disappointed.
- Disappointed?
- Yes.
Then I have nothing else to say.
- I think I said everything...
- Wait.
I needed to say to Leia.
This really isn't right, Leia.
- Listen.
- What am I supposed to say here?
- I understand.
- But...
- Wait. Everyone.
- No.
- I really...
- I understand.
I'm not trying to get you to make up.
I'm not trying to mediate.
- Everyone has their own perspective.
- Right.
- They had their own reasons...
- for making that choice.
- Right.
- I'm sorry if I was too aggressive.
- Let's not...
- judge her right now.
- Okay.
We were just here...
- to share our own thoughts.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yes.
- So, right now...
But we don't have anything
to talk about anymore, right?
- We have nothing to talk about.
- Why not?
Can't we discuss the future?
That's over.
Please explain that to him, Leia.
I don't know what to say anymore.
Siseon said things to me...
that I felt like Team Red would say.
I thought it was Maillard talking.
(Luna, Influencer)
How could he berate me then...
I mean, how could he think that way?
"Oh, he really can't think
from someone else's perspective..."
"because he's so ingrained
in being part of that group."
When Siseon was on Team White
in the beginning,
he was so different from me...
in that he wanted peace for everyone.
I was the one saying,
"It's only important that we live."
The way Siseon is now.
Since I was the leader and all.
But seeing him like that now...
It's not that I felt that he had changed,
but I did think,
"People are weaker than situations."
I felt so resigned.
So I resent Siseon now.
I'm sorry.
But I honestly do feel that way.
- I think it was irresponsible.
- Okay.
But I don't think
it was the right time to say so.
Okay. I got it.
Okay.
They were so close.
Luna was the leader of Team White.
I was the bad cop.
Siseon was the good cop.
Luna balanced us.
The other team members
fought hard in their own ways too.
Hamlet would quietly share his thoughts.
Boss would be running around.
Paul would be running around.
We have those memories with Luna.
Seeing them like that
in a different situation...
The situation itself was sad.
(Leia, Journalist)
I didn't control my emotions well.
(Siseon, Gender equality activist)
There's a right time to say something,
but I chose the wrong time.
I feel really bad,
and I want to apologize.
- I said I'd respect her decision.
- Sounds good.
Good job.
That must've been hard on you, Leia.
I did choose this side.
Anyway, now that it's been decided...
- Yes.
- It's been decided.
But, now that I think about it,
- the diamonds won.
- Right.
- Right? We won, guys.
- Yes.
I'm sorry,
but you can't let your guard down.
Leia.
Leia, this is what's going to happen.
Thinking about that
makes me want to vomit.
- Why?
- Don't overthink it.
If you do so...
(Maillard, Cooking YouTuber)
Then, I wondered,
"Were my actions..."
"too focused on winning?"
"Was it..."
"too unfair?"
"Did I really deprive them..."
"of any ways to take action
the past few days?"
All of these thoughts
went through my head.
I did those things...
for the victory of our alliance,
but I thought...
I got too obsessed...
and greedy.
Processing those thoughts...
took some time.
Maillard's decisions were so aggressive.
He's coming.
I must've gotten way too obsessed.
- No, but that's the right thing to do.
- But if this were reality...
- You did your best.
- Yes.
I think I got too obsessed.
- But this is...
- I get that you're torn.
I think it taught us a lesson
that too much of a good thing...
is not always good.
I brought ruin upon myself
by being too greedy too.
But we weren't too greedy...
We were just preventing unknown risks.
- Right.
- No.
I feel like I should've at least
given them some breathing room.
They did have a way
to do some damage on us today.
- Right.
- During the trade,
they could've run over here.
- Run over and...
- But I...
I even thought about that.
- Because...
- That's why...
I was extra anxious then.
I even thought about that.
What if I had fallen on my way over here?
What if Mokgye went in first
and waged war?
- If that happened...
- I don't know. I really...
I have no idea, though.
Thank you for your work.
Gosh, this is really...
But Maillard, you did a good job.
Right. We were being smart.
Only Team Red has all members alive now.
I know.
It's time for dinner.
- Do you want to eat something?
- We need a meal.
This party celebrates war.
I've wanted to have this at least once.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Thank you for your work.
We really look so devious.
We're like psychopaths
who enjoy a meal after winning a war.
- We use swear words.
- Right.
- Cheers.
- Thank you for your work.
- You've been through a lot.
- Cheers.
- We did our best.
- Thank you for your work.
Good.
I just wanted to feed them,
so I was grilling some meat
standing next to them.
Still,
while eating and talking,
everyone looked relaxed,
and the mood lightened up.
So I was relieved.
I'm completely drained.
I'm so out of it,
I don't even know what I'm eating.
Still, you ate quite a lot.
I do know I'm eating something.
You do know?
I've been eating well here all the time.
Even after killing my team members,
I ate well the next day.
It's all right.
I hope I can leave here
with the prize money in my hands.
We never know.
This is an announcement
from the Community Center.
The leader negotiation will be held soon.
Since Team Gold's leader left,
Luna, the final survivor,
automatically has become the leader,
for your information.
(Sighing)
Gosh, I have to go
to the leader negotiation?
This is an absolute nightmare.
Goodness.
I shouldn't have said
that I wanted to stay.
Shall we drop by?
Is everyone really gone?
Luna.
- Have you eaten?
- Yes.
- Did you have the leftovers?
I thought it would be nice
if you had something warm.
I'm fine.
Still, take this, just in case.
- It's okay.
- What?
See you later.
- See you. Are you all right?
- Yes.
I'm okay.
She needs some time.
She needs to eat to carry on.
We just wanted to make a living,
but it ended up like this.
The last leader negotiation
will be held soon.
All team leaders, please gather
at the Community Center.
I'm so wasted on beer.
I've got nothing to lose.
That's nice.
If you mess with me, you're all dead meat.
Right. Darn it, stop it now.
- Stop it, please.
- Leave our Leia alone.
Don't start getting interesting
right when it's time to leave.
(Occupied: Please wait.)
The thought of seeing Luna
makes me scared.
Gosh, it's been a long day.
This is the last night here.
Right. It's the last leader negotiation.
But I feel...
like something is missing. Why?
- Hi.
- Hello.
Isn't Team Gold's leader coming?
- She should come.
- She's going to be here.
- Give me 1,250 dollars.
- Stop it.
I want to lose.
Take out the last digit for real.
Hello.
All leaders,
stand at the designated spot, please.
The last leader negotiation...
will now begin.
After Luna entered,
there was silence for a while.
Due to various situations
that have happened so far,
we kept silence, I guess.
First, here's the pollution index...
for the entire Community Town.
The total pollution index
accumulated over the past eight days...
is 79.
Until Day Nine,
when every schedule is over,
the total amount of normal credit
hasn't reached 100.
You succeeded in maintaining
the stable pollution index.
Today, you'll have
the last leader negotiation.
The negotiation on aid and sanctions,
the last agenda, will be held.
Team Red requests a diamond aid
from Team Blue.
I agree.
- I agree.
The decision on the aid has been made.
The leader of the team to provide aid,
please insert the resources into the slot.
From Team Red to Team Blue,
a total of 12,500,096 diamonds
are provided as aid.
I was dumbfounded.
I realized everyone
shared it down to the penny.
The resources are showing
in both teams' resource screens.
All negotiations are complete.
We'll move on to today's life submission.
It really weighs on my mind.
She should submit the life left.
No, she doesn't have to.
I took it from her.
She only had one.
She only had one, and it was taken?
I threw the bomb.
Right.
It weighs on my mind even more
because Luna is the one left.
That's why Luna said she wanted to stay.
Why?
She wanted us to see
that she was left behind.
She did?
- Yes.
- She's mad at us, so she's doing that.
Please check the contents
of the central box...
and assign lives
to the residents of your choice.
(The last survivor of Team Blue: Pitou)
Still, all members of my team survived,
just like my original goal.
We succeeded.
I don't care about the prize money.
(Life Submission for Day 8)
(The last survivors of Team Red:
Donkey, Maillard, Izaha, Siseon)
Please check the contents
of the central box...
and assign lives
to the residents of your choice.
(Life Submission for Day 8)
When I submitted the last life,
(Leia, Journalist)
I had to pick Paul, and then me,
and the reality hit me hard.
Was it the only solution?
I don't think either side is to blame...
for things getting this far out of hand.
The idea crossed my mind...
that I wanted to stop.
Team White submits its lives.
Still, surviving to the end...
is building trust in myself.
So I submitted the lives as I planned
and left.
Your life submission is complete.
(The last survivors of Team White:
Leia and Paul)
You've been through a lot.
Without a problem
and according to my plan,
I submitted the lives.
Luna didn't say anything.
- During the sanction too?
- She said nothing.
- She...
- Did she just go back alone?
She entered,
stood there...
saying nothing,
and just left after everything ended.
She didn't have to submit life.
Goodness.
I felt so conflicted.
She was alone suffering,
and that image...
broke my heart so much.
That's how I felt.
It broke my heart.
The announcement on the last day...
was sent to the dormitory.
Please check the announcement
at the dormitory.
Here it is.
Here's the announcement.
Gosh, I...
can't lose this game.
Tomorrow is the final voting day
for the Community Town.
I will announce the schedule
for the last day.
First,
the last leader reappointment
will be conducted.
After the leader reappointment ends,
the resource distribution
per team will take place.
We have time for distribution.
Second,
the last leader selected...
should visit the Community Center...
distribute all diamonds, gold pieces,
lives, and credits...
that exist as resources for each team...
to individual residents,
leaving nothing behind.
The result of the distribution
will be revealed to each dormitory.
- So leaders distribute those.
- Yes.
Getting them out of the war...
was huge.
Otherwise, I would have been...
a little anxious.
Let me see.
This is the absolute highlight.
After resource distribution...
Third, residents who received
the resources distributed...
are given one last chance for relocation.
Then the personal resources distributed...
can be taken along for relocation.
Fourth, after that,
Team White and Team Gold...
will issue the last resources.
- "After that."
- They can mess with it...
- at the end.
- Team White can do that.
Team White and Team Gold
will issue currency...
for the last time before the last vote...
for one time.
Since it's after distribution
for individuals,
it will be distributed
as soon as it's issued.
The currency issued...
will be distributed only
to the residents of those teams.
The resources distributed
will be announced...
to the dormitory of those teams,
and the amount of gold pieces issued...
can be checked at every dormitory.
(The amount of gold pieces finally issued)
The amount of gold
is revealed, but not mine.
- Right.
- It's whether I'm trusted or not.
If they don't trust me,
- Yes.
- they could all issue gold.
So, if Team White's leader...
blows it out of proportion,
the only one who can betray
everyone else...
and move on...
- is Team White's leader.
- That's right.
They gave the leader
one last chance to backstab.
Team White's leader...
What's happening?
I'm the one pulling the strings.
Fifth,
a vote will be conducted
so that diamonds or gold pieces...
will be received as the final prize.
The resource selected by the majority
in the last vote...
will be chosen as the prize.
The resource decided
will be converted into Korean won...
and will be paid out based on
each individual's holdings,
and the resource not chosen will vanish.
I will explain the final voting format.
In the Community Town, one life equals...
the life of a single resident.
Every resident is given one base vote.
Per life that each resident possesses,
one extra vote is given.
- Yes.
- You got it right.
So, doing it this way
was correct after all.
Goodness, Maillard.
- Maillard, your prophecy is insane.
- I know.
It's one life.
During the final vote, residents...
can purchase
the offensive and defensive rights...
for your values code...
and use them immediately.
I knew it. There's no way
we wouldn't use the values card.
Per one credit, you can purchase...
one offensive or defensive right.
After your credits are used up,
you can make an additional purchase
using diamonds or gold pieces.
However, the cost for additional purchases
will be deducted from the total prize.
If the values codes of the resident...
targeted by the offensive right
are guessed correctly,
that resident will be stripped...
of both the base
and the additional voting rights.
(The offensive right)
Each defensive right negates
one successful offensive right...
executed against the holder.
Multiple offensive
and defensive rights can be used...
and regardless of when they're used,
they will be applied in a lump sum
after all voting is over.
Who has many credits left?
It's Pitou.
Pitou originally had 2, and won 3
as the spoils of war, so 5 in total.
- She can attack five times.
- I see.
How many credits do I have?
How many for each?
Now, Team Blue...
- has a lot of resources.
- Resources.
Is it possible to have
many defensive rights?
Yes, you can have them
as many as your credits.
Honestly, between us,
there's no reason to attack and defend.
There's no reason to do it, really.
We're not doing it for money.
When the final voting time comes,
residents will visit
the Community Center one by one...
and exercise their voting rights.
After the voting is over,
all residents won't go back
to the dormitory.
Each of them will wait in a separate area.
After all residents
are done with the voting,
in the separate areas they're waiting,
they will check the result
of the final voting...
and the individual prize money.
Then,
practically,
I've won!
I just don't know how to lose.
If they don't mess with the issuance,
- it's already over.
- I know.
It's not fun at all. What shall we do?
No, don't change.
Don't change into someone else.
Just hold on for a moment.
But your calculation was correct.
If we had sat on the bomb and dawdled...
and let our guards off,
- they could have won...
- Right.
If they went
for production activities today,
mined lives,
won the war and all,
- they could have made things different.
- Right.
And since they knew personal codes,
- if they attacked...
- Right.
And if we had not waged war yesterday,
- we couldn't have taken eight lives.
- I know.
Those eight votes...
- could have gone to Team Gold.
- Yes.
- We could have lost.
- That's right.
- Then Team Gold could have won.
- They actually stood a chance.
If they had won the war,
they actually could have won this game.
That's how the picture is painted.
This is irritating.
I thought, "Siseon was right."
We just gave it up.
If we had just made our move
earlier today,
if, as soon as we had mined lives,
we declared war on the team...
that seemingly had
the most resources and won the war,
we could have had a shot at winning.
This is crazy.
The last resource issuance is a killer.
They might feel anxious about it
and choose gold.
The sheer power
of the selected currency, so to speak.
Did you see the rule card?
- Is it you, Siseon?
- Yes, we did.
This is our last night together...
The weather got so nice.
The air feels so fresh too.
- Yes, it's so nice.
- This is the perfect temperature.
The only variable we have now...
- is Leia. If Leia...
- Right.
If you don't issue additional currency...
Just as much as you've been doubted,
you'd issue
additional currency tomorrow, right?
- Hey..
- Answer me.
Donkey.
Donkey, you shouldn't stay here.
You need to look at Black's rule book.
You need to bring your supervisor now.
- Shall I bring him now?
- Okay.
Vector.
Coming.
- Did you receive the rule card?
- Yes.
- Can I see it?
- Okay.
- Do they have the weapon dealer's rule?
- No.
Is it okay to show this?
The prices of offensive
and defensive rights for value code...
are set by the weapon dealer,
and the amount will be paid
to the weapon dealer.
The prices of offensive
and defensive rights...
can be set within the total supply
of existing diamonds and gold pieces.
And zero price cannot be set...
since it fundamentally breaks the game.
After all the schedule ends,
the weapon dealer's prize money...
will be split through the agreement
by the weapon dealer and the ally.
So if they purchase defensive rights,
the cost comes to us.
I see.
Maybe we don't need to show this.
How about only earning
the cost of the additional gold pieces?
- I don't think we need to show this.
- Let's not overdo it.
(They don't share
the weapon dealer's rule.)
But there was nothing special.
Why are you avoiding my gaze?
I'm afraid you might betray me tomorrow.
I'll only buy defensive rights tomorrow,
just in case.
Black knows my code, so I'll buy it.
Right.
- Black knows my code.
- He's coming.
Right. I forgot about Black.
- Hello.
- Is your rule book the same?
- It's the same, isn't it?
- It's the same.
- Is it?
But while reading this, I felt...
that if Team Gold...
did their best and kept their resources,
they could have betrayed us.
Pitou.
If we had lost the war yesterday,
we would have lost the whole game.
- Right.
- I heard that too.
It's only the 16 votes' difference.
- That's right.
- Really.
Therefore, all wars were necessary...
- from our perspective.
- I know.
- We had no choice but to wage war.
- Team Gold...
might not understand this.
However, now that
we have the final rule book here,
- every single war was a must for us.
- Exactly.
It has always been that way,
without exception.
That's true.
But people won't go crazy...
and make huge additional purchases, right?
Still,
defensive and offensive rights
won't make much difference.
How much is each one
when buying with resources?
This isn't a vote...
but an offensive right,
so it doesn't mean anything.
Unless all of us
miraculously guessed right,
even if a single person is missed,
it makes a tie.
- You can only buy the offensive right?
- Yes.
- Therefore, she's the only wildcard left.
- Right.
- We cannot check the diamonds.
- Yes.
Leia is the heroine for tomorrow.
Would Leia, who cried today
because of war...
This was exactly why...
we couldn't trust Team White.
- You're right.
- Because they could execute at the end.
- Yes.
- That's why we were with Team Red.
Of course.
It turned out pretty much like
as we expected.
Just how Maillard expected.
I'm relieved that it's Leia.
- Definitely.
- Yes.
She's the one who would suffer
the most if she betrayed.
- You're right
- Yes.
- I'd love to chase the fun,
but so many principles have been
compromised on this show.
I'm going to stick to the principles
at least at the end.
- That's good.
- Don't worry.
It's over now.
I'm so happy.
Everyone, salute to Leia.
No, don't.
- I'm counting on you.
- Princess Leia.
Thank you in advance.
I'm going to get up to speed
on these final rules as fast as I can,
so I can boost my chances of
taking my share in Team Gold.
I considered it as zero percent.
I just wanted to leave a message.
I'm going to keep fighting
to the very end,
even if I have to do it alone.
Just like they said.
Day Nine has begun.
You can change your leader from now.
Teams with a change in leadership...
are requested to have both
the current and new leaders...
visit the Community Center together...
to complete the handover procedure.
In addition,
Aside from leader change,
final relocation,
resource issuance,
and the final vote,
no other Community Center functions
will be in operation.
Please take note of this.
Since there's no trading session today,
the Platform won't be accessible.
That's all
from the Community Center for now.
Lesson learned.
Try to have it all,
and you lose it all.
If you never give up,
even to the bitter end,
your chance at victory will come.
I've learned many lessons.
All good. My goal was to survive
until the end.
Seeing how
all of my team members survived...
makes me feel relieved.
Once reappointment is done,
we shall go to vote immediately, right?
I guess we'll move on to the next step.
Now for the leader redistribution.
Yes.
The discussion time
for leader reappointment has ended.
We'll now start
the final resource distribution.
The leader of the Team White
should now go to the Community Center...
and distribute...
all of the group's diamonds,
gold, lives, and credits...
to each individual member,
leaving nothing behind.
Team White's members
get half the prize money.
It's only me and Paul.
We had 25,000,098 diamonds.
So we'll get 12,500,000 each.
For 98, I'll give Paul a hundred more.
We'll get one life and credit each,
and for the 75 gold,
we'll divide them into 37 and 38.
Paul, I gave you 98 diamonds more.
Since Team Blue is a one-person group,
the distribution
has been completed automatically.
Team Gold and Black is a one-person group.
So the distribution
has been completed automatically.
The safest thing is for me...
is to be the only one left in Team Red.
- For the final relocation?
- Yes.
Why? What's the risk then?
Siseon might relocate to Team White.
If they issue one billion...
- when Paul, Leia, and Siseon are there...
- One billion?
But they're relocating
after the resource distribution.
- But...
- If they issue again,
they can distribute again.
The final currency issuance...
gets distributed
within the team immediately.
I see.
Team White is lucky.
If they'd been playing
super exclusively up to now,
they might have pulled something.
That's right.
It seems like they're keeping variables
in play until the very end.
Yes. Can we trust Team White?
Can we trust Team Gold?
We should've sent Izaha too.
- To Team White?
- Yes.
If we doubt them.
I see.
I'm going to put in...
one last safeguard.
- For me...
- Pitou!
- Yes?
- I'm going to put in one last safeguard.
- What's that?
If Izaha fails to relocate to Team White,
we should all vote Team Gold.
Why is that?
If Team White gathers...
and issues extra currency,
all the previous team members
of Team White will get the dividends.
Yes.
So we're going to ask them
to accept Izaha.
I'm a hostage too, aren't I?
Go together.
- I'll be here.
- Isn't it better to divide?
- Send...
- Izaha will go to Team White.
- Yes, leave him here.
- Siseon will stay in Team Red.
Yes, but him being here is his choice.
So if he requests to relocate,
you'll be going
even if we don't want to send him.
- Okay.
If they accept Izaha...
Decide after talking about it.
She might not accept it
if she doesn't understand.
Okay.
For me, Team Gold isn't bad too.
- Do as you wish.
- That's what I'm saying.
- I have nothing to lose.
- So I'll send Izaha.
If they don't accept,
I'll put all my votes to Team Gold.
Okay.
He's removing even the last bit of risk.
He's going all in until the end.
I know.
He's very smart.
- Leia.
- Yes?
I'll put one last lock.
I'm relocating Izaha to Team White.
- Izaha? Sure.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- It doesn't matter.
Am I not trustworthy?
Well,
we made it this far because
we kept each other in check.
- Yes, this is the last check.
- The last check.
- He says it's not.
- Cool.
We didn't come this far
by trusting each other?
- No, not with trust.
- It was trust for me.
We came here by risking each other.
You're right.
We had hostages in our teams.
- Holding each other's lives.
- It's good to do this until the end.
You're doing your best.
From the start,
no strategy in Community Town
has ever been built on trust.
Trust is all broken.
We've made it this far...
by calculating the minimum risk...
and agreeing on how to split it among us.
Would Team Red and Black consider this?
They would.
There.
Even when I asked a girl out,
I never went this far.
I distributed zero diamonds to Donkey...
and 12,500,000 diamonds to Izaha.
Siseon also received 12,500,000 diamonds.
I have the remainder.
If Team White declines to accept Izaha,
I'll vote for Team Gold.
It's to distribute the risk.
If Izaha stays in Team Red,
I told Leia
that we will support Team Gold.
In the end, it finishes with blood mixed.
You're right.
Prepare to relocate.
(Final resource distribution is complete
and last relocation starts.)
I'm requesting to relocate to Team White.
I accept. Welcome!
You've accepted the relocation.
Izaha from Team Red relocated
to Team White.
Final relocation.
Izaha, please relocate within one hour.
- You're here.
- I'm here.
- Our room is...
- Fancy living room.
- the largest.
- Nice!
It's larger in size.
- We have a nice view.
- Welcome.
My goodness.
The view is spectacular.
Now, hold on to Siseon.
Block him from getting out.
I'm not going out!
He might relocate.
Lock him in the bathroom.
Izaha is the only one who relocated.
For the final?
The final relocation is over.
Now residents can't ask for relocation.
The final resource issuance will begin.
Please wait.
Will Team White understand my intention?
I'm just fighting until the end.
(Dormitory for Black)
I didn't want to bring this up,
but let me tell you something.
There's one variant.
Vector...
can set the price for the offensive right.
The offensive right...
can deduct the prize money
the same as gold.
But the prize money will come to us again.
To Vector and me.
The weapon dealer should decide...
the price for values code
and the offensive right...
in terms of gold and diamonds.
Yes.
(1 hour ago)
Did you...
set your resources?
Not yet.
Luna might burn everything.
It's good for us.
Shall we leave it as is?
I want to give Luna a choice.
- Okay.
- If that's what she wants.
I thought of making it expensive.
But then it'll mean we're giving...
- no choice for Luna until the end.
- You're right.
If we set 1 for 10,
- it's reasonable.
- Yes.
Let's set as 1 for 10...
I'll set the price of...
values code offensive right
and defensive right.
For diamonds,
it'll be five million diamonds.
Ten gold pieces.
Luna has 37 gold pieces,
so I figured 15,000 dollars
would be a huge win...
and set the price at ten gold pieces.
For diamonds, I used the same value.
That's 5,000 dollars' worth of diamonds,
which comes to five million diamonds.
The prices have been set.
You may now leave.
Good work. Thank you.
(Offensive and defensive right prices:
5 million diamonds, 10 gold pieces)
Here are the prices of the offensive...
and defensive rights available
during today's final vote.
If you purchase
an offensive or defensive right,
the value of that resource will be
deducted from the total prize money.
Please keep that in mind.
At least we'll be able to do something
at the very end if we want to.
- Right.
- Yes.
- If we were to issue it now...
- Right.
- We're going to issue gold now, right?
- We're doing it now.
So it's based on the current amount.
The baseline is 200 gold pieces...
because I haven't issued any.
Good thing I didn't issue any yesterday.
What, 500? Seriously?
The final resource issuance...
for Team White and Team Gold begins now.
That's really expensive.
The leader of Team White must...
bring the resource issuance voucher
and the stamp...
to the Community Center...
- and decide how many diamonds...
- Let's just...
- to issue one last time.
- not go.
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
Good luck.
The leader of Team Gold must...
bring the resource issuance voucher
and the stamp...
to the Community Center...
and decide the final amount of gold
to issue.
(Final resource issuance)
If you wish to issue diamonds,
enter the quantity on the voucher...
and submit it to the central box.
(Diamond issuance)
I've never betrayed the trust...
of anyone I've worked with.
I stayed loyal...
to every alliance...
because only then,
could I land one decisive blow...
at the critical moment.
When Team Blue declared war on us,
Team White lost...
three of our valued teammates.
As for Team Red,
they never actually declared war.
They always killed by proxy.
So I believe they are guilty...
of turning Team White and Team Blue
into war criminals.
Izaha did join our team,
but he worked hard,
so I wanted to reward him more.
I also wanted to respect Luna's choice...
to remain with Team Gold until the end...
and send a message to those...
who declared war and launched bombs...
against a threat that wasn't even real.
Team White's leader, Leia.
I will issue diamonds one last time.
(Diamond issuance)
No diamonds were issued.
You may now leave.
(No alliance lasts forever,)
(but neither does any cycle.)
(Still dreaming of peace...)
(0 diamonds)
With this,
Luna could take all the prize money
and win for sure.
Team White can't issue any more...
because too many people
have a stake in it.
If you wish to issue gold,
enter the quantity on the voucher...
and submit it to the central box.
We're done for now.
We could now lose by a single vote
because we got complacent!
- But now...
- This last bit of complacency!
I'll issue one trillion gold pieces.
The final resource issuance is complete.
The final vote will begin shortly.
Until then, all residents must wait
in their dormitories.
We're done for. She issued one trillion?
As soon as I heard the announcement,
I knew something was wrong.
I knew Team White was too entangled...
in conflicting interests to issue more,
but Team Gold only has one member.
If she issued a huge amount of gold,
she could use it to buy...
more offensive rights
and attack endlessly.
I should have seen this coming.
During the war, we set the war cost...
before we could issue more currency.
I think this follows the same logic.
They held the currency issuance...
after individual allocations
and relocation were complete.
Then Team White can't issue more.
Everything is already distributed.
But if I issue gold like crazy now,
its value becomes worthless, right?
That was the strategy I kept planning
when I wanted to start a war.
Then I can attack endlessly, right?
The moment I saw it, I knew we'd lost.
I was certain. Luna had made up her mind.
Team Gold would gain
nearly unlimited offensive rights.
It probably won't greatly affect
the actual prize payout.
Even if she attacks 10 million times
or 100 million times,
the actual prize might drop
by only 50 dollars.
Issuing that much currency means...
she plans to attack every value code
and win.
Team Gold will win with just one vote.
Team White now...
has a psychological barrier
to issuing any more,
so I concluded we couldn't win.
With no conflicting interests,
Team Gold is guaranteed to win.
Does Team Diamond know they've lost?
They must all know, right?
So we shouldn't vote for Team Gold.
- She issued one trillion gold pieces.
- Right.
But what are those 200 gold pieces?
- Those 200 were the initial issuance.
- The original issuance.
- Because of the initial issuance?
- Yes.
Exactly. Congratulations
on one trillion gold pieces.
That's cute.
- She's trying to send a message.
- Definitely.
"Don't even think about coming over!"
It's a message. A message.
"I don't want anything from you."
"We lost."
"It's not that you didn't choose me."
"I made sure you couldn't choose me."
I think that was the message
she wanted to send.
Issuing all that gold...
felt like firing a warning shot.
Everyone in the other dorms could see it.
So I was really nervous on the way there.
Then I came back and found a flower
waiting for me.
If they fully understood my position...
and the strategy behind it,
I think they might accept it.
But I don't think they realized...
the rules gave me one last option.
They'll probably see it as a betrayal.
So I felt a little bad about that.
Let me run through one scenario.
There's no winning scenario.
With this setup, we have no way to win.
Isn't this basically tying our hands...
and killing us?
Gosh.
What? I'm the only one who came out ahead.
I got complacent too.
I should've told Vector
to issue zero diamonds.
The vote to determine the final prize...
and individual value code targeting
will now begin.
Residents must visit the Community Center
one at a time...
to vote and target a value code.
Let's do this!
To stop Team Gold from running wild,
whoever held the casting vote
also had to hold the gold...
and both sides had to promise...
not to devalue it. That might've worked.
If that person said,
"I'll trust you on this."
"Don't issue any gold."
As a show of trust?
Then she might not have issued any.
Leia, check your personal resources,
mark your final ballot,
and submit it to the central box.
If you wish to purchase an offensive...
or defensive right, state the quantity.
With your current credits, Leia,
you can purchase one right.
The cost of additional purchases
will come out of the total prize money.
I'll use a credit to buy
one offensive right.
Please collect one offensive right.
"Target name"?
This really feels like
I'm killing someone.
I'll try attacking...
(Leia's choice: Vector)
Vector.
But will it work?
To prepare for the worst,
I should've used it on Team Gold,
my direct competitor,
but I didn't want to do that.
I had one either way,
so I thought about who was the worst
out of everyone here.
(Leia, Journalist)
I thought, "Let's try targeting Black."
"Ability" is maxed out.
"Practicality" is maxed out too.
"Result."
Has he ever made a utilitarian choice...
(Values Code Offensive Right)
Please submit the offensive right
to the central box.
Sorry, Vector.
I went for it.
A total failure.
Your attack has failed.
If you wish to buy more,
please state the quantity.
I won't purchase any more.
Please proceed with
the final resource vote.
I had 1 base vote and 1 life,
so that was 2 votes for diamonds.
I had two votes.
I think it'll turn out as expected.
I don't think there'll be any surprises.
(Paul's personal resources)
I'll use one credit on defense.
That's two.
(1 base vote and 1 life: 2 diamond votes)
(Izaha's 1 base vote:)
(1 diamond vote)
I'll buy five defensive rights.
(Pitou's 1 base vote and 4 lives:)
(5 diamond votes)
I'll use 6 credits
to buy 6 defensive rights.
I'll use 50 gold pieces
to buy 5 defensive rights.
The 50 gold pieces have been...
- deducted from the prize money.
- Okay.
(Maillard's 1 base vote and 9 lives)
Plus...
(10 diamond votes in total)
Ten.
Why don't I have anything?
(Donkey's 1 base vote:)
(1 diamond vote)
(Siseon's 1 base vote: 1 diamond vote)
I'm counting on you.
I'll spend 1 life to buy 1 extra vote.
I'll use a credit...
to defend myself, even if it's pointless.
It may be pointless,
but I'll do it for Team Diamond.
Honestly, if Leia had acted faster,
I'd feel bad for the others,
but I would've issued a massive amount...
and bought an absurd number
of defensive rights.
I wondered whether Luna would win
once those two fought it out...
or if they used five million diamonds...
to buy around two offensive rights,
we might make another 20,000 dollars.
I waited for the result,
hoping that might happen.
(Offensive and defensive right prices)
(Final personal resources)
I will use 98 gold pieces
plus 2 more with credits...
to buy a total of 100 defensive rights.
I know 100 sounds completely absurd,
but I calculated how many I'd need
if one person held all those resources...
and used them to attack me.
I'll use gold...
to buy 8,898 offensive rights.
The requested quantity is too large.
We don't have
enough printed offensive rights.
They'll be issued to you in stages.
If you repeat the same attack,
write down the number of repetitions
and submit it.
The number you enter will be applied
to the attack,
and that amount will be deducted
from the prize money.
The prize money...
This is going to take forever.
Again. Slowly.
So it's 1-1-1, 1-1-1.
I accidentally wrote 1-2-1.
(Values Code Offensive Right)
It's 2-1... It's 2-2-2.
This is just about combinations.
Multiply them out,
and there are 64 per person.
I even had a rough idea
of their Majority Rules Game choices,
so I used that as my baseline.
But Team Red had always feared...
having their values codes targeted,
so I considered that they might've...
deliberately chosen answers
different from their own beliefs.
I entered 100 repetitions per attack.
(People backed into a corner will bite.)
(At least one person survives.)
(That person can reduce your prize
to 1 cent.)
(The moment our numbers dwindle,)
(we're much more likely
to act aggressively.)
When will I ever finish this?
This is driving me insane.
It was just a reality check.
(Luna, Influencer)
Until yesterday, I'd felt this way
about the majority alliance.
"Why are they taking it this far?"
But I kept asking myself
the same question.
I was checking every possible outcome...
and writing each one down.
My hands were shaking,
so I couldn't even calculate.
I kept making mistakes.
Why am I taking it this far?
I don't even want all the prize money.
I just want everyone to split it evenly.
What started this fight?
What made us shut each other out?
It was a sobering reality check,
but I still wouldn't change my decision...
and kept trying so hard.
I felt this strange disconnect.
They were all B choices.
All about Meaning.
It made me wonder whether...
they'd truly been making choices
to seek Meaning...
and how much people judge things...
based on their circumstances
and the lives they've lived.
I chose Ability because I lived...
in a world where having it
meant I could use it.
If I'd lived in a world
with limits like this...
of course I would've chosen Structure.
Seeing so many B choices
made me think about that.
It seemed like they'd made choices...
that leaned too heavily
toward Practicality.
So what did any of it mean?
Your attack was successful.
Please proceed with
the final resource vote.
For the final resource vote,
each resident receives one base vote...
plus one additional vote
for every life they hold.
Luna, you have...
one vote in the final resource vote.
(Final resource selection)
This is an announcement
from the Community Center.
The final currency vote results are in.
- Gold has been selected.
- Gold?
(Final selected resource: Gold)
What?
What is this?
(Final selected resource: Gold)
What?
Luna worked hard for this.
Leia, your final prize is as follows.
(Current value per gold piece:
0.000000075 dollars)
(Gold held: 37, final prize: 0 dollars)
It didn't feel real. I just went, "What?"
(Leia, Journalist)
Gold?
So she tried until she got it right.
Was it one trillion?
She issued that much until she got it.
This is why you should never upset anyone.
This is why
you should never corner anyone...
or upset them.
(The current value of 1 gold:
0.00000075 dollars)
Oh, my gosh.
Luna, talk to you never!
I shed so many tears for you.
Because you disgraced my tears,
you're unforgivable.
After one trillion gold pieces
were issued,
I gave up.
Luna isn't trying...
to end game like this. It's a relief.
Honestly, I'm very offended.
It's a reasonable choice for Luna.
But I blame the system.
I'm kind of stunned.
I never expected that from Luna.
Honestly, I didn't think she'd do that.
So,
I'm kind of sick of people right now.
Just people in general, not just her.
I'm sick of people as a whole.
(Leia, Journalist)
That was expected of Luna.
That was very typical of her. And I am...
actually pretty happy.
There is something regrettable.
In the current system,
Team White's leader...
may feel pressured...
to issue additional resources.
Now that Donkey's bound
to receive a prize,
he'll remain alone in Team Red.
We need at least one person on the team.
So I'm moving to Team Blue.
Then aside from Donkey in Team Red...
and me in Team Blue,
everyone has moved to Team White.
In that situation,
no matter how much
Team White's leader issues resources,
its members will receive...
the equal amount of the prize.
As long as I give up on taking the prize,
it'll be a good idea.
The plan where eight people
divide the prize equally...
didn't include me.
Because when I first submitted
the proposal,
it was distributed to seven people
without me.
Then when Leia saw that,
she said it'd be best
to distribute it to eight.
So it was fixed.
It'd be nice for me
to take the prize, but...
(Maillard, Cooking YouTuber)
I want to bring a definite result...
for my teammates...
who trusted me
and participated in my plan.
I feel bad for them
that I didn't see that coming.
This is an announcement
from the Community Center.
According to the final currency vote,
gold has been selected.
Here is Luna's final prize.
(Final prize: 75,000.18 dollars)
I found the whole situation ridiculous.
Even though I never planned to
take the prize to myself,
that's what happened.
The value of each gold is ridiculous.
Those ridiculous numbers were
utter nonsense.
This could've been avoided.
At first, we were like,
"Let's all survive together."
"Let's all take the prize home together."
Then we suddenly declared
unnecessary wars...
and killed people unnecessarily.
I felt deflated.
Despite that,
I made it.
All schedule in the Community Town
has come to an end.
Goodbye.
The weapon dealer's
final accumulated prize...
is 24,999.82 dollars.
The weapon dealer and the ally...
will split the prize
through the Ultimatum Negotiation.
The weapon dealer...
will suggest the ratio of the prize...
he'll split with the ally.
If the ally accepts it,
the prize will be given...
according to the ratio
the weapon dealer suggested.
However, if the ally doesn't accept it,
neither the weapon dealer
or the ally can have the prize.
Please check the prize...
and suggest the ratio.
I'm ready to set the ratio.
Here is the prize...
the weapon dealer suggested.
(He suggested exactly half.)
If you accept
the weapon dealer's suggestion,
you will both receive the prize.
- Twelve thousand...
- The ally agreed to your suggestion.
Yes!
You will both receive the prize.
- I get to take something home.
- All schedule in the Community Town...
has come to an end.
Goodbye.
For example, here's what's possible.
If you're a leader
and the group split into two,
there will be a moment...
when you need to sacrifice
one of your members.
I'm never going to sacrifice anyone.
I'll stay with you to the end.
That is something I can't promise, though.
Because only then,
this system can keep going.
I hope I can be seen as...
one of the believable representations
of humanity.
It reminded me of dilemma questions
I'd forgotten about.
In the past,
if I believed I had to be moral...
and uphold the values one should have
as a decent human being,
now, I've adapted to reality.
Because I've experienced it.
Some of the memorable questions were...
whether to force an innocent person
to sacrifice...
in order to avoid multiple sacrifices.
Something like that.
The answer I had in my mind was...
different from the actual choice I'd make
in that situation.
I was asked to answer questions...
that I never could have
imagined how I'd answer.
That was the most memorable part.
I think political influence is about
persuading people of the value behind it.
Rather than going, "You need to
recognize me because we were close."
"It's a matter of loyalty."
Should I call it important values?
Or goals?
There must be a baseline.
It's up to me to persuade them...
and agree with me.
I think people suppress the evil
inside them.
I do have evil inside.
Because I have the desire to find out
how evil I can be,
I'm looking forward to participating
in this show.
I wonder how evil I can be.
I hope I'm not someone
that make people go,
"What is wrong with her?"
I hope I don't have to torture myself.
You know what they say.
If you chase money, you can't make money.
If you follow your heart,
money will follow you.
Like the saying goes,
if I win people's hearts,
I'll survive to the end.
Being transparent is the best.
It keeps the organization stable.
However, domestic companies
don't like to be transparent...
about their internal situation
to external shareholders.
That is one of the reasons
the stock prices were low until now.
Society in general
should be transparent...
for people to trust one another.
I believe trust is the force...
that drives nations
and organizations forward in the end.
I think transparency is
a very important value.
This kind of problem occurㄴ...
because you can't predict
the other person in the game.
What influences that the most?
And I think that is reputation.
If the other person's strength is one,
ordinary people criticize others
four times more.
People don't like to
compliment each other.
It's hard to build up your reputation,
but it only takes a moment
to bring it down.
Because everyone likes to gossip.
If you want to be good at politics
in the end,
you need to know
what the other person wants...
and how you can help them.
You can't help
but understand the other person...
and think about the situation they're in.
Rather than surviving,
I'm here to understand people.
Games? I normally play...
games that require cooperation.
If I lose an individual match,
it's entirely my fault.
Whereas for a team match,
I can blame others.
It makes me feel better.
That helps me stay mentally strong.
In the end, you play games for fun.
(The Community 2: Invisible Hand)